嘿,美女
Hey, sexy.
我喜欢那裙子
I love that dress.
当然啦,洛伦佐 这就是你做的
Of course you do, Lorenzo. You made it.
- 嗨,甜心 - 你们好
- Hi, sweetie. - Hey, guys.
- 你在那儿啊 - 莉娜
- There you are. - Lena.
- 你又干成了 - 哦,都是为了你啊,布拉德利
- You've done it again. - Well, it's all for you, Bradlee.
该过去玩玩了
Gotta mingle.
哦,姑娘们在水池边
Oh, the girls are by the pool.
哎呀,哎呀,哎呀,莉娜,你的小情郎躲哪儿去了？
Well, well, well, Lena. So where's this sexy boy toy of yours hiding?
我不知道你是橄榄球迷,帕特力克
I didn't know you were a football fan, Patrick.
我从不看比赛,我只是特别爱他的老内衣广告
I've never watched a game. I'm just a big fan of his old underwear ads.
他大概刚冲完澡,我这就去揪他出来
Well, he's probably just getting out of the shower. Let me go hurry his ass up.
- 嗨 - 嘿,宝贝
- Hi. - Hey, babe.
最 长 的 一 码
第四节开始,欧文斯要掷球了,他给了大空档里的布朗！
Start of the fourth quarter, and Owens will throw. He's got Brown wide open!
你肯定是在逗我玩
You have got to be kidding me.
亲爱的,让我看完这场比赛吧,我会带你去看电影的
Honey, just let me finish the game, I'll take you to the movies.
带我去看电影？
Take me to the movies?
拜托！楼下正在大聚会
Hello! There's a huge party going on downstairs.
还记得餐车和停车服务员吗？
Remember the catering trucks and the valet parkers?
哦,该死,我忘记了
Oh, shit, I forgot.
我来告诉你该忘记什么
I'll tell you what you should forget about.
橄榄球
Football.
因为有了它你就会什么都忘掉
Because it's forgotten all about you.
现在,你这醉鬼
Now, you're going to put this outfit on that I bought you,
快穿上我给你买的衣服到楼下去
drag your drunken ass downstairs
像好孩子一样陪陪我的客人
and mingle with my clients like a good boy.
我是谁？埃尔顿·约翰吗？我才不穿这鬼玩意呢
Who am l? Elton John? I ain't wearing that shit.
- 你要穿的 - 我可不是你训练的猴子,亲爱的
- Yes, you are. - I'm not your trained monkey, honey.
对啊,你比猴子可贵多了
No. You're much more expensive than that.
不过听我说
But I tell you what.
要是五分钟以后你还没下楼
If you're not downstairs in five minutes,
我就要让你滚下我的床
I'm gonna throw you out of my bed,
滚出我的家,滚出我的生活
out of my house and out of my life.
然后你就得自个儿买香蕉吃了
Then you're gonna have to pay for your own bananas.
我生气是因为你没穿我的礼物
I'm just so mad at you because you're not wearing my gift.
礼物？
Gift?
什么礼物？
What gift?
给爱人的礼物咯,我把它放在壁橱里了
It's like a l-love-you gift. I left it in the closet for you.
真的？
Really?
保罗,我太激动了
Paul, I'm so excited.
想不到你会给我送礼
I can't believe you did this.
- 你放在哪儿了？ - 在后面,右边
- Where'd you put it? - In the back, on the right.
保罗？保罗,你干什么？
Paul? Paul, what are you doing?
我看咱们都需要单独待会儿
I think we need some alone time, honey,
所以我打算开你那辆本特利去兜兜风
so I'm gonna go take a cruise in your Bentley.
混蛋醉鬼,你敢开我的车？
Don't you dare take my car, you drunken bastard!
- 你是我的人！ - 我是爱你的人
- I own you! - I love you.
来人啊,把这该死的门开开！帕特力克？
Somebody please open this damn door! Patrick?
- 莉娜？ - 帕特力克
- Lena? - Patrick.
你出什么事了？
What happened to you?
他把我锁在壁橱里就不管了
He locked me in the closet and left me to die.
上帝啊,他疯了！
Oh, my God, he is deranged!
他以为他可以捉弄我
He thinks he can mess with me.
911.
哦,捣乱的家伙来了
Oh, man. Here come the party poopers.
哎呀,哎呀,哎呀,假如这不是保罗·克鲁,那我就是见鬼了
Well, well, well. I'll be damned. If it isn't Paul Crewe.
我做错什么了？我是不是违章驾驶了？
So, what did I do wrong? Was I driving poorly?
没有,没有,有人报告说这车被偷了
Nope. Nope. This car was reported stolen.
不,不,不,其实这是我女朋友的车
No, no, no. It's actually my girlfriend's car.
真见鬼
Shit happens.
是见鬼了,我是说,瞧瞧你那耳朵
Shit does happen. I mean, look what happened to your ears.
我得问问你,他就用那耳朵听XM Radio？ （一家卫星广播公司）
I gotta ask you something. Does he get XM Radio with those?
确实能听到几个频道
Actually, they get a couple of channels.
这是保罗·克鲁
It's Paul Crewe.
那么还有一个问题
Another question, though.
圣诞老人 他长什么样？
Santa Claus. What's he like?
小伙子,我不想逮捕你这样的名人
Boy, I hate to arrest a public figure like yourself,
不过我想,你现在
but, hell, I don't think you got too many
没有太多公事要办吧？对吗？
endorsement deals to worry about, now, do you?
听着,弗罗多先生,别小看我
Now, listen here, Mr. Frodo. Don't get short with me.
很棒,我是说,他很棒
That was good. I mean, he's good.
老兄,希望你有很多钱来玩这场游戏
Man. I hope you got a lot of money for that game you threw,
因为这是我见过的最惨的事了
because that was the most pathetic thing I ever saw.
现在下车吧,克鲁先生
Now, step out of the vehicle, Mr. Crewe.
你不觉得我该把车开过去一点吗？可能会被人蹭到的
Don't you think I should pull the car over more? I could get sideswiped.
你口齿不太清楚,保罗今晚一直在喝酒？
You're slurring your words a bit there, Paul. You been drinking tonight?
绝对没有,帮个忙好吗？拿着这个,我倒一下车
Absolutely not. Now, could you do me a favor? Hold this beer while I back it up.
嘿,你就把那罐喝完吧,我还有五罐呢 保重,哥们
Hey, you can finish that one. I got five more. Take care, guys.
我们正在处理3-94情况
We got a 3-94 in progress.
好的,冷静
Okay, remain calm.
你好吗？好吗？好吗？好吗？
How you doing? What's up? What's up? What's up?
现在您看到的是实况直播,警方正在追逐
What you are watching is live footage of a vehicle, apparently stolen,
一辆明显是被盗的车辆
being pursued by police.
我们现在得到消息说,这辆车的司机
We're receiving word now that the driver of that vehicle
是匹兹堡的前橄榄球明星保罗·克鲁
is former Pittsburgh football star Paul Crewe.
您可能记得
Crewe, you might remember,
克鲁是唯一因为在职业橄榄球赛中打假球
was the only man ever to be indicted on federal racketeering charges
而遭到联邦的诈骗罪起诉的人
for shaving points in a professional football game,
尽管此事从未被完全证实
although it was never fully proven.
Yeah！
Yeah!
- 喂 - 不准再刮伤我的车
- Hello. - Do not get one more scratch
要不然我就割断你的喉咙
on my car, or I will slit your throat.
你瞧,我们的问题就在这儿
See, that's our problem, sweetie.
你对这车比对我们俩还要关心
You care about this car more than you do us.
再说你怎么知道这宝贝已经被刮伤了？
And how'd you even know there was a scratch on this baby?
因为我就在电视上看着你,全国人民都在看
Because I am watching you on TV, as is the whole country.
你又一次向所有人证明
Once again, you are proving to everyone
你是个一文不值的垃圾
what a worthless piece of shit you are.
啊,但愿他们喜欢这样
Well, I hope they like this.
嘿,莉娜！
Hey, Lena!
我想可以正式分手了！
I think we should start seeing other people!
我想我是爱上某人了
I think I'm in love.
好消息,小伙子们,我没把啤酒洒出来
Good news, boys, I didn't spill my beer.
毫无疑问,今晚克鲁严重违反了
Without question, Crewe's five-year federal probation for point-shaving
五年假球缓刑期中的限制规定
has been severely violated tonight.
这位曾红极一时的橄榄球明星,看来前途非常黯淡
The future of this once-great football star looks very dark indeed.
这下远离大城市了吧？大明星？
Long way from the big city, huh, superstar?
在这里过日子吗？
Staying with the times around here, huh?
她是不是很美？
Ain't she beautiful?
到家了,孩子
Home sweet home, boy.
站起来
Get on your feet.
你是个幸运的狗杂种,克鲁
You're one lucky son of a bitch, Crewe.
- 是吗？ - 是的
- Is that right? - That's right.
典狱长很爱橄榄球
See, the warden loves his football.
事实上,你那次的比赛,他支持的是赢球一方
Fact, he was on the winning side of your little thing.
- 哦,那要恭喜他了 - 可我没有
- Well, tell him congratulations. - But I wasn't.
欢迎来阿伦维尔
Welcome to Allenville.
谢谢你,警长,从这里开始就交给我吧
Thank you, sergeant. I'll take it from here.
- 下午好,犯人克鲁 - 啊
- Afternoon, inmate Crewe. - Yeah.
来吧,典狱长要见你
Come on. Warden wants to see you.
咱们走
Let's do it.
快走
Move it.
我自己在大学里也打过一点球
I used to play a little college ball myself.
在迈阿密大学
Down at the University of Miami.
你肯定有很多老队友给关在这里
I bet a lot of your old teammates are locked up in here.
我的老队友里没有犯人,倒是有几个看守
No inmates from my playing days. Couple of guards, though.
瞧,我们这里有个很棒的狱警联盟
See, we got us a fine prison-guard league down here.
就像公司垒球队
It's like a company softball team.
现在,典狱长@@
Now, the warden@@
…他想叫你帮个忙
@@he's gonna ask you to help out.
好啊,帮什么忙？
Okay. With what?
那可不好
That wasn't nice.
典狱长问你的时候
When the warden asks you,
你要怎么说？
what are you gonna say?
行？
Yes?
你要对他说“不”,明白吗？
You're gonna tell him "no." You got it?
你要对典狱长说
You're gonna tell the warden
你不想和他的橄榄球爱好扯上关系
that you want nothing to do with his football fantasies.
不想在我的后院里这么干
Not in my back yard.
因为管这监狱的不是典狱长,是我
Because the warden don't run this prison. I do.
你明白了？
You understand?
没有全明白
Not entirely.
好,我明白了,坏蛋,我明白了
Okay. I feel you, dog. I feel you.
“破坏王”保罗·克鲁
Paul "Wrecking" Crewe.
虽然我不会经常对我的新客人这样说
I don't get to say this to my new guests very often,
不过你能来这里我真是感到荣幸
but it's an honor to have you here at this institution.
被关在这里我也很荣幸,先生
It's an honor to be locked up here, sir.
哦,对了,这是埃罗尔·丹德里奇
Oh, well, this is Errol Dandridge.
山德士上校一直在吃自己的鸡肉 （把他比作肯德基老头了）
Colonel Sanders been eating his own chicken.
他是我的政治顾问
He's my political adviser.
曾有几个非常有影响的人和我接触过
See, I've been approached by several very influential people
问我是否有兴趣当州长
wondering if I'd be interested in standing for governor.
因为他们看到了我对这座监狱的管理,觉得我也许能管理整个州
They see the way I run this prison, think maybe I should run this state.
只不过是鸡奸案少一点,对吗？
Only with less sodomy, right?
我希望是没有
Hopefully none.
对不起
Sorry.
在德克萨斯州我们对两样东西特别重视
Now, there are two things we take very seriously here in the state of Texas.
监狱和橄榄球
Prison and football.
在这里我们也打一点橄榄球
We play a little of the latter here.
典狱长太谦虚了,不肯承认他的球队非常好
The warden is too modest to admit that his team is rather good.
但是好得不够
But not good enough.
上次夺冠是在五年前
Five years since our last championship.
五年了
Five years.
我千方百计通路子
Now, I've worked real hard, pulled strings,
托了很多人情才把你搞到这里来,保罗
called in quite a few favors to get you here, Paul.
那么,你愿意干吗？
Now, why would you go and do that?
因为我相信你能让我们重回正轨
Because I am convinced that you can get us back on track.
我自己都不记得有多久没打橄榄球了,我真的不想干
I haven't played football in I don't know how long. I don't really want to.
你不用打比赛,保罗,只要当顾问就行
You wouldn't be playing, Paul. Just consulting.
当选过国家橄榄球联盟MVP的人
Anyone who was once the MVP of the National Football League
肯定能提供很多专家意见
must have a great deal of expertise to offer.
队长,假如让克鲁先生用他的经验来教导我们
Captain, what would you say to Mr. Crewe looking in,
你有什么意见？
giving us the benefit of his experience?
我觉得这是很好的主意,典狱长 可以利用我们能够获得的一切帮助
I think that's a real good idea, warden. We can use all the help we can get.
好,那么就全妥了
Well, then, it's all settled.
你怎么说,保罗？
What you say, Paul?
我很感谢你的邀请 但是我想放弃
I appreciate the offer, but I'm gonna have to pass.
我可以向你保证
Now, I can assure you
只要你参加,你在这里的日子就会轻松得多
that your time here will be a whole lot easier if you just participate.
我只想自己过完日子然后回家,没别的了
I just wanna do my time and go home. Nothing else.
请你见谅,克鲁先生
If you'll excuse us, Mr. Crewe.
科纳瓦队长,你留一下
Captain Knauer, you can stay.
坐下！
Sit down!
我以前很喜欢你做的内衣广告
I used to love your underwear commercials.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
我前夫穿的紧身衣就是那种牌子
My ex-husband wore the same brand of tighty whities.
不过不像你能把衣服撑得那么满
He didn't fill them out quite as well as you, though.
特效,好莱坞的把戏,不全是因为我
Special effects. Hollywood. Not all me.
哦,我非常怀疑
Oh, I doubt that very seriously.
好,那就让他变得热心,妈的！
Well, then get him enthusiastic, damn it!
来吧,起来.
Come on, get up.
怎么样？现在全搞定了？
How'd it go in there? We all set now?
对啊,我们配合得真好
Oh, yeah, we're real tight.
只给你最好的,大明星
Only the finest for you, superstar.
开玩笑而已
I was just playing.
我不会忘记你的,克鲁
I ain't gonna forget you, Crewe.
嘿,你那场比赛害我输了钱,混蛋！
Hey, yo, you owe me money on that game, punk!
你最好当心点,橄榄球先生！
Better watch yourself, Mr. Football!
婊子！
Bitch!
对,你最好逃,娘们
Yeah, you better run, woman.
喂,橄榄球
Yo, football.
坐吧
Take a seat.
谢谢
Thanks.
知道吗,我还从没见过哪个犯人
You know, I have never seen one inmate just walk in here
一进来就让所有人都恨的
and be unanimously hated by the entire population.
- 从来没见过 - 我怎么会这么走运？
- I ain't never seen it. - How'd I get so lucky?
你可以抢银行、贩毒
You could have robbed banks, sold crack,
偷你奶奶的养老金,没人会在乎
stole your grandmama's pension, and nobody would have cared.
可是在橄榄球赛里打假球？老兄,那可不是美国人干的事
But shaving points off a football game? Man, that's just un-American.
- 你打橄榄球？ - 我？不
- You play football? - Me? No.
我太没用,他们以前先挑白人,孩子再挑我
I suck so bad, they used to pick me after the white kids.
他们还曾经被我搞到发疯,心想： “真不敢相信,我挑了个不会打球的黑鬼”
Used to be mad too. It's like, "l can't believe I picked a nigga that can't play."
- 我叫凯尔泰克 - 保罗·克鲁
- Caretaker. - Paul Crewe.
你想要什么我都能帮忙
Whatever your pleasure, I can facilitate.
你想要大麻,想要冰毒-- 或者想要百忧解,找我就对了
You need weed, you need meth-- Hey, you need Prozac, I'm your man.
我知道你们白人总是得忧郁症
I know how you white boys always deal with that depression.
我是说,从我个人角度来看
I mean, me personally, I don't understand what you white boys
我不明白你们白人都在忧郁个啥 嘿,你是白人啊,笑一笑
all depressed about. Hey, you're white. Smile.
稍微付点报酬,我连麦当劳快餐都能帮你搞到
And for a small fee, I can even get you McDonald's.
- 真的？ - 对,Mickey D的
- Really? - Yeah, that's right. Mickey D's.
我兄弟汉堡包埃迪有门路
My man Cheeseburger Eddy got the hookup.
汉堡包埃迪？
Cheeseburger Eddy?
没错,可以给你吃麦旋风
That's right. We can get our McFlurry on.
吃吧,胖子
Enjoy it, fat man.
能搞到漂亮女人的爱情吗？
What about the love of a beautiful woman?
哦,那你得降低一下
Well, you're gonna have to lower your standards
关于漂亮的标准和关于女人的标准
on the beautiful part and on the woman part.
嘿
Hey.
咱们还是只谈汉堡包吧
Let's just stick with the cheeseburgers.
啊,他们现在是挺丑,但是过了八个月 你就会觉得他像碧昂斯（当红女歌星）
Oh, they ugly now, but in eight months, he gonna look like Beyoncé.
不,谢了
No, thanks.
那,现在是最重要的问题
Now, here's the most important part.
你不能让这些家伙吓住,不能让他们瞧不起你
You can't let these guys scare you. You can't let them punk you.
因为要是你那样做了,你最后就会变成别人的婊子
Because if you do that, you gonna end up being somebody's bitch.
那我可不要,谢谢你的忠告
Don't want that. Thanks for the advice.
嘿,我帮你把盘子拿走吧
Hey. Let me take that tray out for you.
我还没吃完呢
I ain't done eating yet.
哦,没吃完？那我还给你
Oh, you're not? I'll give it back to you, then.
你死定了！
You're dead!
马蜂窝！
Hornet's Nest!
全都趴着别动
Everybody stay down.
不许出声！
Stay quiet!
来吧,克鲁,起来
Come on, Crewe, get up.
起来,大明星
Get up, superstar.
是,长官
Yes, sir.
你以为在这儿想干什么就能干什么,是吗？
You think you can do anything you want around here, don't you?
哈,你跟管这地方叫“家”的其他垃圾
Well, you are no different than any other piece of shit
没什么两样
that calls this place home.
真的？这些家伙也觉得你是个乡巴佬？
Really? These guys think you're a dumb redneck too?
小妞,那是你的新绰号
Girl, that's your new boo.
最好收回你那一套,已经不新鲜了
You better cut that shit out. It's getting old.
这下你死定了
That's gonna cost you.
我盼着呢
Looking forward to it.
醒一醒,睡美人
Wake up, Sleeping Beauty.
嘿,鸟人
Hey, superdick.
典狱长想知道你在蒸笼里呆过以后是不是改了主意
Warden's wondering if your stay in the hotbox has changed your mind.
我在这里多久了？
How long have I been in here?
一个星期 想呆两星期吗？
One week. Wanna go for two?
话说回来,你是怎么找到这些家伙的？
How'd you find these guys anyways?
招募的,孩子
Recruitment, boy.
大学里的明星要是没进职业队,总得有个地方去
When college stars don't get drafted, they need a place to go.
有工作,有钱,有社会保险
A job, money, security.
谁他妈把佳得乐都喝了？
Who drank all the damn Gatorade?!
该死的！
Damn it!
显然还有类固醇
And apparently steroids.
你看,你好像已经得到了 你想要的所有人才 为什么还需要我？
Look, seems like you got all the talent you'd want. So why do you need me?
啊,你可能觉得难以置信
Well, now, you might find this hard to believe,
监狱联盟里有些人对我不太喜欢
but there's folks here in the prison league don't care for me very much.
- 你？典狱长？ - 他们觉得在第一场比赛
- You, warden? - They thought it might be amusing
就安排我们和联盟冠军打,会很有意思
to schedule the defending league champs as our first game.
而我呢？我觉得你这样的职业老手
And me? Well, I thought an old pro like yourself
也许能提供一些训练的诀窍、高招、秘方
might have some training-camp tricks, drills, insights to offer up.
让我们有竞争优势
Give us the competitive edge.
好的,这比较简单,你需要一场热身赛
All right. Relatively simple. You need a tune-up game.
热身赛？
A tune-up game?
对 在大学里,我们每个赛季开始时 都会跟阿巴拉契亚的队
Yeah. In college, we'd start every season against Appalachian State
或是什么很烂的二线队打
or some slack Division ll team.
把他们打得屁滚尿流,鼓舞一下队员的自信心
Kick the living shit out of them. Get their confidence up.
你知道吗,保罗？
You know something, Paul?
- 你刚给了我一个灵感 - 太好了 是什么？
- You've just given me an inspiration. - That's great. What?
你要组一支队来和我们打第一场比赛
You're gonna assemble a team to play the first game against us.
而你,克鲁先生,将是四分卫
And you, Mr. Crewe, are gonna be the quarterback.
我不同意
I don't think so.
听我说
Let me tell you something.
在我的监狱里,要想过下去,你就得照办
In my prison, to get along, you gotta go along.
我只想蹲满三年然后走人
I just wanna do my three years and be done.
在袭击科纳瓦队长之前,你的刑期是三年
Three years is before you assaulted Captain Knauer.
现在,你可能要陪我们很长一段日子了,克鲁先生
Now, you could be with us for a very long time, Mr. Crewe.
好吧,我干
Fine, I'll do it.
正确选择
Good choice.
不过有一个条件
But one condition, though.
你要答应不让科纳瓦队长暗算我
Gotta promise me to keep Captain Knauer off my back.
那就说定了
It's a deal.
那么,你有四个星期来组一支队并训练他们
Now, you got four weeks to assemble a team and train them.
什么,我们是不是每天只能用软球练半小时？
What, are we gonna have a half-hour a day to practice with a Nerf ball?
哦,在这些大墙以内,我保证让我的人给你充分的自由
Oh, I'll make sure my boys allow you sufficient freedom, within these walls,
来使你的球队成型
to get your team in shape.
这是什么？“橄榄球先拔？”
What's this? "Football 'tree-outs."'
什么叫“先拔”？
What the hell is a "tree-out"?
“选拔”,你个笨猪
"Tryout," you half a meatball.
- 这橄榄球是怎么回事,哥们？ - 克鲁正在组一支球队
- What's this football thing about, man? - Crewe's getting a team together.
- 跟谁打？ - 看守
- To play against who? - The guards.
我不知道你们都是怎么想的,不过我有时会有冲动
Now, I don't know about y'all, but I occasionally have the impulse
想要揍一揍我们的某位优秀管教人员
to physically assault one of our finer correctional officers.
哦？那到底怎么才能做到？
Yeah? Well, how the hell we gonna get to do that?
在“先拔”上亮一手就行了,你个大呆瓜
Just show up at the "tree-outs," you big, dumb bitch.
女孩子也能打球吗？
Do the girls get to play?
我们打的是橄榄球,不是卵球
We're playing footballs, not balls-balls.
这是放屁 只不过又给看守一个机会来打我们
This is bullshit. Just another chance for the guards to beat on us.
你们这些白痴还不明白？我们可以放开手脚打那些看守
Don't you idiots get it? We could get a free shot at the guards.
这下轮到我们出手了,我们可以把他们胖揍一顿
This is our turn. We could beat up on them.
我们可以宰了他们
We could kill them.
宰了他们
Kill them.
你们都知道,MVP把自己的队友出卖了
You know MVP sold his own teammates out.
你们觉得他会对你们这些傻瓜干什么？
What do you think he's gonna do to you fools?
这才是真理,上面还有些奶酪呢
And that's the truth. With some cheese on it.
这两片屁股中间可没肉饼
There ain't no meat loaf between these buns.
喂,那是我的布告,老兄！费了好大劲做的！
Yo, man, that's my flier, man! I worked hard on it!
看见了？他像个小婊子一样跑了 对吧？你看见了,对吧？
You see? He ran like a little bitch, right? You saw that, right?
哦,球队需要你 球队需要你
Yo, team needs you. Team needs you.
你-- 你来参加--参加先拔吧
You sh-- You come to the tr-- Come to the tree-outs.
蹩脚场地,垃圾器材@@
Crappy field, shit-ass equipment@@
嘿,老兄,至少那边有几个世界级选手
Hey, man, at least we got some world-class players over there.
四十五
Forty-five.
四十六
Forty-six.
四十七
Forty-seven.
他说不定能撑起这支球队
He might make the team.
好啊,假如要把他刷下来,就由你去说
Well, if we gotta cut him, you're doing it.
四十九
Forty-nine.
五十
Fifty.
- 好,老兄 - 干得好
- All right, man. - Good job, man.
好,好,好,你是橄榄球运动员？
Well, well, well. You a football player?
啊,不 从没打过橄榄球,先生
Oh, no. I never played no football, mister.
那么,是怎么回事？你看了布告,觉得这比较好玩？
So, what happened? You read the flier, thought it looked like some fun?
- 哦,我不识字 - 哦,没关系
- Oh, I can't read. - Oh, don't worry.
读书是有钱人的事
Reading's for rich people.
那么你知道,我们正在组织橄榄球队,欢迎你加入
So you know, we're putting together a football team. Love you to join.
你会教我打橄榄球？
Will you teach me to football?
我们当然会教你打,对吧,凯尔泰克？
Sure we'll teach you to football. Won't we, Caretaker?
嘿,我什么都会教你,只要别吃了我就行
Hey, I'll teach you anything. Just don't eat me.
好啊
Okay.
放下,史瑞克,放下！ （把他比作怪物史瑞克了）
Down, Shrek. Down!
好,来吧 想参加球队选拔的都起来
Okay, bring it in. Whoever's trying out for the team, wake up.
拿出点精神给哥们儿看看好不好？
Can you give a brother a little hustle?
很好
Very good.
可能有人还不知道我是谁,我是保罗·克鲁
For those of you who don't know who I am, I'm Paul Crewe.
我将是你们的教练,你们的队长,你们的四分卫
I'm gonna be your coach, your captain, your quarterback.
你有几年没打球了,为什么不能让我打四分卫？
You haven't played in years. Why can't I be quarterback?
- 说得对 咱们看看你的本事 - 好啊
- You're right. Let's see what you got. - All right.
- 扔过来,我接着 - 传,传！传！
- Hit me, I'm open. - Hike, hike! Hike!
这就是为什么,现在坐下,闭上你的嘴
That's why. Now, sit down and shut up.
是滑了一下,我刚才吃爆米花来着
It slipped. I just ate popcorn.
提问：先生们,有谁以前打过橄榄球？
Question: Any of you gentlemen ever play football before?
- 你打过？在哪儿？ - 堪萨斯州队
- You did? Where? - Kansas State.
你耍我吧？在施奈德教练手下？
Are you shitting me? For Coach Snyder?
堪萨斯州立监狱队
Kansas State Prison.
我听说那儿的床垫最软了
Now, I hear they have the softest mattresses out there.
没错,是这样
Yeah, they do.
不如西德克萨斯精神病院的软
Not as soft as the ones at West Texas Mental lnstitution.
- 真的？ - 有话咱们以后再说吧
- Really? - Let's finish this conversation later.
现在,我要看看你们的水平
For now, I wanna see what you got out there.
从一到十给他们打分
We'll grade them on a scale of one to ten.
快啊！加油,加油,加油！
Move it! Hustle, hustle, hustle!
给这些人六分,给这些人五分
Give these guys sixes. Give these guys fives.
好,好,给他们三分
Good. Good. Give them threes.
非常好！
Very nice!
- 是不是漏了谁？ - 堪萨斯州队的那家伙呢？
- Aren't we missing somebody? - Where's the Kansas State guy?
你们这些混蛋最好别把我刷下来！我还在这队里呢！
You assholes better not cut me! I'm still on this team!
负二
Negative two.
好的,就给他负二
All right, go with negative two.
嘿！来人,给我一瓶节食可乐！
Hey! Somebody bring me a Diet Coke!
- 来吧！ - 好的！
- Let's do this! - That's it!
五分
Five.
好 七分
Good. Seven.
笨蛋轮胎！你这破烂胎！
Stupid tire! You're a fricking tire!
你以为你比我强？我要揍扁你！
You think you're better than me?! I'll kick your ass!
三分
Three.
再加半分？
And a half?
行,那比较好
Yeah. That's better.
好的,很好
Okay. Good.
对,撞那沙袋,你上,老兄
Yeah. Hit that bag, man. There you go, man.
四分
Four.
- 五分 我不知道 - 我上
- Five. I don't know. - I go.
上吧,斯韦托斯基！
Come on, Switowski!
爸爸！
Daddy!
哦,厉害！
Oh, man!
- 瞧瞧 - 他把沙袋从链子上扯下来了
- Look at that. - He got it off the hinge.
- 我看该打十分 - 那就打十分吧
- I think that's a ten. - Let's go with a ten.
对不起 我“打破破”了你的玩具
I'm sorry. I "brokeded" your toy.
没关系,那很好,你该和凯尔泰克拥抱一下
No, that's a good thing. You should have a victory hug with Caretaker.
什么？你说什么？嘿！
What? What you talking about, man? Hey!
混蛋！
Asshole!
好,伙计们,这很简单,你们做一次钮扣钩
Okay, fellas, it's pretty simple. You do a buttonhook.
你们其余的人替我阻挡,剩下的我来解决
The rest of you guys block for me. I'll take care of the rest.
好吗？上,上
Okay? On "go." On "go."
预备？开始！
Ready? Break!
我们慢慢来吧
We'll work on that.
好,用一般速度,慢一点,别着急
Okay, half speed on this one, guys. Slow and easy.
预备？
Ready?!
开始！
Go!
停下！
Stop it!
停止暴力行为！
Stop the violence!
我们不能和平相处吗？
Can't we all get along?
- 嘿,保罗 - 昂格尔
- Hey, Paul. - Unger.
- 球队看起来很棒 - 哦,是啊
- Team's looking great. - Oh, yeah.
- 你也是 - 对,正在努力
- So are you. - Yep. Working on it.
看守们会像古代巴比伦那样血流成河
The blood of the guards is gonna flow like the rivers of ancient Babylon.
那是好消息,昂格尔,你真好
That's good news. Unger, you're the man.
今天干得很好 你们开始像个样子了
Good job today. You're all starting to look really sharp out there. Yeah.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
- 我们会很惨 - 是啊,毫无疑问
- We're gonna suck. - Yeah. No doubt about it.
看来你们需要一点帮助
You look like you could use a little help.
不是我笑话你,老兄,你看来有点年头了
No offense, my man, but you're a little seasoned.
有点年头？
Seasoned?
我不是想打球 我想做教练,我是内特·斯卡波罗
I'm not asking to play. I'll coach. I'm Nate Scarborough.
内特·斯卡波罗？
Nate Scarborough?
是俄克拉荷马的海斯曼奖杯获得者？
The Heisman Trophy winner from Oklahoma?
是D区牢房的囚犯
The inmate from cellblock D.
不过,大概在一百年前我还能跑能打的时候
But about a hundred years ago, when I could run and gun,
我确实是俄克拉荷马州人
yeah, I was a Sooner then.
我听说你已经死了
I heard you were dead.
不,我没死,我一直在这里发臭
No, I ain't dead. I've been right here, rotting.
等待一个机会,回敬那些虐待狂看守
Waiting for a chance to get back at those sadistic guards.
等着,这个机会
Waiting. For this.
那么,教练,你也看到了
Well, coach, as you can see,
这里的精英其实没有和我们合作
we don't exactly have the cream of the crop to work with here.
那我们该怎么办？怎么才能找到球员？
Well, what are we gonna do? How are we gonna find players?
他们怎么让你进佛罗里达州队的？
How'd they get you to go to Florida State?
他们把我招进去的
They recruited me.
我去找人来
I'll get the strippers.
哦,林赛,这不是关于赞颂或祝贺的问题
Well, now, Lindsay, this isn't about credit or congratulations.
这是关于给失足者一个机会
This is about giving men who've made mistakes in their lives
让他们改过自新
an opportunity to rise above themselves.
走出铁窗的问题
To move beyond the bars of containment.
说什么？
Say what?
我要对你做什么
What I would do to you.
好,踢得好,小子
Yeah. Nice boot, skin man.
嘿,为什么让他踢球？我可是国家级选手
Hey, why does he get to be the kicker? I was All-State, man.
咱们看看你的本事
Let's see what you got.
这就是为什么,蠢驴
That's why, you dumb-ass.
还是去跑圈吧
Just go do some laps.
我听说你们找我有事
I heard you boys needed to see me.
对,我介绍你认识斯基奇
Yeah. I want you to meet Skitchy.
嘿,老兄,到那幢房子里去看看吧
Hey, dog. Check that building over there.
他们把所有记录都放在地下室里
They keep all the records in the basement.
他在这里呆得太久了,知道每样东西在哪里
He's been here so long, he knows where everything is.
这可不一定是好事啊,对吗？
That ain't necessarily a good thing, is it?
我的假释期在86年,但是我跟看守打了一架,所以@@
I had a parole date in '86. But I got in a tussle with a guard and@@
就一拳,假释就没了
One punch and it went away.
为了一拳就多关二十年？
Twenty extra years for one punch?
他很倒霉,他打的那个看守
Well, unfortunately for him, the guard he punched
如今恰好成了典狱长
just happens to be the warden now.
哦,该死 海岑典狱长？
Oh, shit. Warden Hazen?
“哦,该死”,说得对
"Oh, shit" is right.
院子里有人打架,快派人支援
Fight in the yard. Send backup.
来得正好
Right on time.
- 咱们干吧 - 咱们干吧
- Let's do it. - Let's do it.
有个黑人做朋友,你们很高兴吧？
Ain't you guys glad you got a black man for a friend?
- 是啊 - 走吧
- Hell, yeah. - Come on.
海岑给每个犯人都评了级
Hazen has a rating system for every con.
三星是什么意思？
What's three stars?
犯人的暴力倾向越重,星数就越多
The more prone to violence that the inmate is, the more stars he gets.
最高是五星
Five stars is the max.
我还不知道有这事,瞧瞧我这个疯子得了几颗星
I didn't know that. Let's see how many stars my maniacal ass got.
半颗星？这肯定是搞错了,再看看,再看看
Half a star? That's gotta be a mistake. Check it again. Check it again.
你大概就和一箱子小猫咪一样疯
You're about as maniacal as a boxful of kittens.
什么话？这可不好笑
Come on, that's not funny, man.
我该去捅个人,让我的级别涨上去
I'm gonna have to stab somebody or something. Get my rep up.
那我们今晚就来个疯狂枕头战吧,那可以让你的级别涨一点
Why don't we have a maniacal pillow fight tonight. That could get it up some.
对,我们还可以卖门票
Yeah. We can sell it to pay-per-view.
超级明星对战半颗星
Superstar Versus Half-a-Star.
你给我闭嘴,要不我就割了你的喉咙,看里面的灰尘飘出来
Why don't you shut up before I slit your throat and watch the dust come out.
好啦,哥们,我们只有几分钟时间
Come on, guys, we only got a couple minutes.
这家伙怎样？
How about this guy?
操,这傻瓜上了三次电椅,还没死
Damn, this fool got the chair three times, ain't died yet.
嗯,我们也许得不到最有才华的球队
Well, we may not have the most talented team,
但是肯定有最残忍的球队
but we will definitely have the meanest.
- 他为什么这么干？ - 因为他是个变态
- What's he doing that for? - Because he's a freak.
嘿,大脚怪兽！有人来看你了！
Hey, Sasquatch! Someone's here to see you!
你这样可不太聪明
Not too smart on your part.
嘿
Hey.
撞脑袋好玩吗？
How's the headbanging coming?
你出血了,你自己也知道
You're bleeding. Just so you know.
有人说你和我长得很像
People have told me that you and I look a lot alike,
所以我想自己来瞧瞧
so I wanted to see for myself.
我要去撒泡尿
I'm gonna take a piss.
你把他吓跑了,笨蛋
You scared him away, dumbshit.
开玩笑吧？五星的托雷斯喜欢看“The View”节目？
You're kidding. Five-star Torres likes The View?
不,他只是喜欢乔伊·贝哈
No, just Joy Behar.
好消息是她可以站着喂奶,就这样
The good news is she can breast-feed standing up. That's it.
她怎么会想到这种屁话的？
Where does she come up with this shit?
我自己也是斯妲·琼斯的粉丝,我喜欢那婊子
I'm a Star Jones man myself. I love that big bitch.
那好像是遥不可及的事
That was, like, the furthest thing.
我结婚的时候太年轻了,所以,我是说
I got married so young, so, I mean,
他们没有压迫我,社会没有压迫我@@
they weren't pressuring me, the society was pressuring me@@
托雷斯先生
Mr. T orres.
我们犯人正在组织一支橄榄球队
Us convicts are starting up a football team.
没兴趣
Not interested.
我们和看守比赛
We're playing the guards.
走开
Walk away.
好主意
Good idea.
两个人都不成
0 for 2.
你现在就在压迫她
You're putting the pressure on her right now.
演出结束了,朋友
Show's over, amigo.
我还有15分钟可以看乔伊·贝哈
I still got 15 minutes of Joy Behar.
我把你的时间扣了,回牢房去,混蛋
Well, I'm cutting you short. Back to your cell, asswipe.
嘿,白人小子
Hey, white boy.
切里海德要打球吗？
Cherryhead gonna play?
对,他会打的
Yes, he is.
克鲁,别忘了我会得到空档的
Crewe, don't forget, I'm gonna be open.
绿队40！一！
Green 40! Hut!
该死！
Damn!
布鲁西,布鲁西 你还好吧？你还有气吗？
Brucie. Brucie. You all right? You breathing?
我有一只鸟,他叫罗尼
I got a bird. His name is Ronnie.
哦,告诉罗尼,你被干翻了
Well, tell Ronnie you got knocked the fuck out.
哇,别开玩笑 真要打橄榄球？和看守对战？
Wow, no bullshit. Real football? Against the guards?
真刀真枪
Full contact.
科纳瓦队长是他们的四分卫？
Captain Knauer is their quarterback?
- 对？ - 那我可以擒抱他了？
- Yep. - So I get to tackle him?
对,你可以擒抱他,也可以拿锤子砸他脑袋
Yeah. You can either tackle him or hit him over the head with that hammer.
我只想弄伤他,不想宰了他
I wanna hurt him. Not kill him.
咱们还是快出去吧,免得那东西咬人
Let's get out of here before that thing bites somebody.
好,那就在练习场上见你和你的小鬣蜥吧
All right. We'll see you and your pet iguana at practice.
蹲下,预备！
Down, set!
一！二！
一！
Hut! Hut!
嘿！
Hey!
- 给我 - 解决掉那家伙
- Hit me. - Get rid of it.
解决掉那家伙！
Get rid of it!
他没有解决掉那家伙
He didn't get rid of it.
抱倒你这混蛋了
Sacked your ass.
应该有人跑到空档
Somebody's gotta get open, guys.
你被大锤砸翻了
You got hammered by the hammer.
我是绊倒了,我们得找些有速度的人
I think I felt it on my leg. We gotta get some speed, man.
你指望什么？在这里没人帮得了你
What'd you expect? You got no brothers out there.
你说什么？我们还有斯韦托斯基呢
What are you talking about? We got Switowski.
斯韦托斯基？那算一个
Switowski? That's one brother.
只有一个黑鬼,这可不行
That's a lonely nigga. This ain't hockey.
要找有速度的人,你知道该上哪儿
You want some speed, you know where to go.
嘿,瞧瞧这冒牌的痞子阿姆
Hey, yo, check out this fake Slim Shady, man.
我知道你不能拒绝我的东西
I knew you couldn't resist my shit.
我有混合饮料,美得让你灵魂出窍
I got the shakes that'll make you quake.
我有炸薯条,美得让你喜上眉梢
I got the fries that'll cross your eyes.
我有汉堡包,美得让你--
I got the burgers that'll--
我就是有汉堡包嘛
I just got burgers.
很好,谢谢你
I'm all right. Thank you.
我只是想跟你们说说加入橄榄球队的事
Just wanted to talk to you fellas about possibly joining the football team.
我们只会跟你玩一种游戏,那就是
The only game we'd play with you is
狠抽打假球的白人小子让他哭得像个宝贝臭婊
Slap the Point-Shaving White Boy Till He Cries Like a Baby-Back Bitch.
宝贝臭婊,宝贝臭婊,宝贝臭婊
Baby-back bitch, baby-back bitch Baby-back bitch
- 真是个大傻机器人 - 啊
- That's a big-ass robot. - Yeah.
你帮我个忙,出去一下好吗？
You gonna help me out here?
谢谢,半颗星
Thank you, Half-a-Star.
你们也知道,我们要和看守比赛
Just so you know, we are playing the guards.
那不是球队,只不过是一帮呆瓜
That ain't a team. That's just a bunch of dumb rednecks
找了借口互相乱打而已
giving themselves excuses to grab each other.
这位先生肯定是正宗运动员喽？
This guy must be quite the athlete, huh?
你胆敢闯进这块地盘来是因为你认识我
You risk bringing your ass in the jungle because you know I am.
对,所以你会在一对一的比赛里打败我,是吗？
Yeah, so you'd beat me in a game of one-on-one, right?
- 什么？ - 我看你该走了
- What? - I think it's time for you to get stepping.
这样好吗？就比一场
How's this, though? One game.
我赢了你,你的人就替球队打球 你赢了我,我就再也不来烦你
I beat you, you guys play for the team. You beat me, I'll leave you alone.
应战,应战,迪克
Take that. Take that, Deac.
这傻瓜有种,宝贝
This fool ain't nothing but a thing, baby.
- 球,哥们 - 球来了！
- Ball, dog. - Ball up!
克鲁会打篮球吗？
Can Crewe play ball?
他是天生的运动员
He's a natural athlete.
格雷格·路加尼斯也是,不过我打赌他会完胜的
So is Greg Louganis, but I bet you he'd get his ass whupped out here.
- 打11分 有犯规你要自己喊 - 好的
- Game's 1 1. Call your own fouls. - Okay.
- 上啊上啊 - 给他点厉害尝尝,迪克！
- Come on, come on. - Give it to him, Deac!
我伤到你了？
Did I get you?
没有,不算什么
No, that was clean.
他没事,叫他妈妈来
He'll be all right. Call his mama.
- 假如我对你犯规,就告诉我 - 好的,宝贝
- If I foul you, tell me, dog. - Okay, baby.
尝尝这个犯规-- 尝尝这个犯规
Take this f-- Take this foul.
怎么回事？我看这应该是我的球吧？
What happened there? I think it's my ball, right?
好吧
All right.
起来！起来,迪克！
Get up! Get up, Deac!
加油,保罗！
Come on, Paul!
- 冷静点 - 什么？
- Calm down. - What?
别把弟兄们煽动起来,好啦
Now, don't stir up the brothers, now. Come on.
上啊,迪肯！
Come on, Deacon!
我伤到你了吗,哥们？
Did I get you, dog?
没有,宝贝,那不算什么,防得好
Hell, no, baby. That was clean. Good D.
我以为他不想受伤呢
I thought he didn't wanna get hurt.
那不是受伤的问题,是自尊心
It ain't about getting hurt. It's about pride.
他现在肯定觉得很自豪
I bet you he's pretty proud right now.
做个下流胚也不容易！
It ain't easy being cheesy!
我伤到你了？我伤到你了？
Did I get you? Did I get you?
- 不,我没事,宝贝 - 我没有伤到你,是吧？
- No, I think I'm okay, baby. - I didn't get you, did l?
是你滑倒了,王八蛋
That's traveling, bitch.
你还想来吗？
You keep coming, huh?
到赛点了,宝贝,你希望比赛的高潮是怎样？
Game point, baby. How you want the game put up?
犯规
Foul.
真是混蛋哨！
That was a bullshit call!
我的球场,我的球
My court, my ball.
好了,各位 让迪克来说！
All right, y'all. Let Deac speak!
揍得你很爽,小子
Nice spanking that ass, dog.
- 现在走吧 - 等一下
- Now, get stepping. - Hold up.
你们有跑锋吗？
Y'all got a running back?
没有好的
Not any good ones.
我不想冒犯你,迪克@@
No disrespect, Deac@@
@@不过吃了这种打都能抗住的人
@@but any man that can take that kind of beating out here,
我很想看看他在身体接触运动里能干什么
I can't wait to see what he can do in a contact sport.
妈的,我加入
Shit, I'm in.
把那汉堡包给我,你真是个王八蛋
Man, give me that cheeseburger. You acting like a real McAsshole.
汉堡包,他要跟这白人小子走,就让他走
Cheeseburger, he wants to run with the white boys, we will let him.
来吧
Let's do this.
厄尔·麦吉特
Earl Megget.
好啊,我们没弄到整个巧克力店 但是得到了一块好时巧克力
Well, we didn't get the whole chocolate bar, but we got a Hershey's Kiss.
我接受
I'll take it.
咱们快点结束吧,菜鸟,我饿坏了
Let's get this over with, rookie, I'm starving.
鲜肉,小伙子们！鲜肉！
Fresh meat, boys! Fresh meat!
蹲下,预备！
Down, set!
班涛,你是个神经病！
Battle, you're a psycho!
托尼,你是个肥猪！一！
Tony, you're a fat shit! Hut!
我靠！
Holy shit!
截住他！
Get him!
鞋都跑掉了吗？嘿,经理,你看是不是可以
Ran right out of your shoes, huh? Hey, manager, don't you think
给我们新的明星跑锋弄双像样的防滑鞋？
we can get our new star running back a decent pair of cleats?
好啊,我有个表哥是给锐步开车的
Yeah. I think I got a cousin that drives a truck for Reebok.
太好了,老兄 小点也没关系,还没有我撑不大的鞋
It's cool, man. I never had shoes growing up noway.
- 现在我可好了 - 哦,好
- I'll be all right for now. - Oh, okay.
你这乡下小子快去集合
Get your country ass back in the huddle.
那小子光脚跑得特别快,你看见了吧？
That boy got some slave feet, you see that?
防守！到那边集合！
Defense! Huddle up over there!
保罗,保罗
Paul. Paul.
嘿,女士们 在那边干什么？
Hey, ladies. How's it hanging?
- 告诉他 - 我有话和你说
- Tell him. - I'm gonna say something to him.
我就是想让你知道,我是你的头号崇拜者
I just wanted to let you know I am your biggest fan.
到比赛那天我会拼命给你加油,把这牢房也掀掉
And I will be cheering my jailhouse boobies off for you at game day.
我很感激,谢谢你
I appreciate that. Thank you.
保罗
Paul.
我也很感激你
I appreciate you.
好的,谢谢 听你这么说我很高兴
Okay, thanks. I'm glad to know that.
好,你们完事了吧？
Okay, are you done now?
你出什么毛病了？ 我不给你加油你就吃醋了？
What's wrong with you? Jealous because I don't cheer for you anymore?
我才不知道你在说什么,变态
I don't know what you're talking about, freak show.
随你怎么说,麻皮背
Whatever, back freckles.
对,麻皮背,她在胡言乱语
Oh, yeah, back freckles. She's making up shit now.
我要去喝点水
I'm gonna get some water.
那次专访的效果比我预料的还好
That feature interview worked better than I thought.
我刚和ESPN2通了电话
I just got off the phone with ESPN2.
他们想要电视转播这场橄榄球赛
They want to televise the football game.
看守、囚犯、保罗·克鲁,这些都是吸引眼球的题材
Guards, cons, Paul Crewe, it's compelling stuff.
人们兴趣浓厚啊
Lots of human interest.
别在这里做这个
Don't do that in here.
电视
Television.
丹德里奇,你看这能不能帮我
Dandridge, do you think that might help my visibility
提高在本州选民中的知名度？
with the registered voters of this fine state?
哦,会的
Oh, yes.
怪物回来了！
The freak is back!
嘿,嘿 我又来了
Hey, hey. It's me again.
你知道,要是我把这半边桌子放下来,我们就可以一起玩
You know, if I take this half down, we could play together.
那我就把它放下来了
I'm just gonna take this half down.
别担心,别担心,我还有一个球
Don't worry. Don't worry. I got another ball.
没问题的
It's okay.
你想发球吗？
You wanna serve?
我来发球
I'll serve.
有个很好的消息,我们组织了一支橄榄球队
Really good news. We started a football team.
你喜欢橄榄球吗？
You like football?
和乒乓球有点像
It's kind of like Ping-Pong.
只不过球大一点,是鸡蛋形的,就和我的脑袋一样
Only the ball's a little bigger and egg-shaped, like my head.
说笑而已,别激动
Just a joke. Stay calm.
这样你就有个很好的机会把人扔到地上
Give you a good chance to throw people on the ground,
揍他们,就像你小时候那样,在你长成10英尺6英寸以前
hurt them like you used to when you were a kid, 10 feet 6 inches ago.
我们要和看守们比赛
We'd be playing the guards.
我想约翰大伯就是他们的安全卫
I think Papajohn's their safety.
我要打球
特利,要是没人冲到我身边,回头我们就再打乒乓球,好吗？
Turley, nobody gets to me. We'll play more Ping-Pong later, okay?
一！
Hut!
很有效
Effective.
- 好了 - 他把我鼻子打断了
- All right. - He brokeded my nose.
我不要再打球了
I don't wanna play no more.
嘿,嘿,嘿,斯韦托斯基,你说什么呢？
Hey, hey, hey. Switowski, what are you talking about?
这是橄榄球啊,受点伤难免的
This is football. Shit happens.
保罗,他把我鼻子打断了
Paul, he brokeded my nose.
好啦,别哭了
Okay. Stop crying.
好啦,这个我们能治好的,来了
All right. We can fix this. Here we go.
好,很好,很好
Okay. Good, good.
看上去怎样？
How's it look?
看上去怎样？看上去-- 看上去好像--好像比以前更好了
How's it look? It looks-- It looks like-- It looks better than before.
- 真的？ - 对,更加直了
- Really? - Yeah, it's straighter.
更加漂亮了,有点像年轻时候的麦克尔·杰克逊
More distinguished. Kind of like a young Michael Jackson.
我爱小麦克尔
I love little Michael.
那很好,那很好
That's great. That's great.
我看他是故意的
I think he did it on purpose.
不,他不是故意的
No, he didn't.
好吧,也可能是
Okay, maybe he did.
你该向他道歉,来吧,特利
You gotta apologize to him. Come on, Turley.
说对不起
Say you're sorry.
好啦,说吧
Come on. Say it.
对不起
他说对不起了,我让他说对不起了
He said he's sorry. I got him to say he's sorry.
对,对 我们都很感动
Yeah, yeah. We're all impressed.
看来不错,先生们,都很努力
Looking good, gentlemen. Way to work hard.
练得真好,保罗！我和姑娘们想让你看看
Good practice, Paul! Me and the girls wanna show you
- 我们的练习成果 - 好啊,让我看看
- what we've been practicing. - Okay, hit me.
来吧,上了 一、二、三
Come on, let's go. One, two, three.
给我一个@@
Give me a@@
D,D,给我一个I I,I,给我一个C
D, D, give me a I I, I, give me a C
C,给我一个--
C, give me a--
好了,好了！我看到了,到比赛时候再亮出来吧
All right, all right! I got it. Just save it for the game.
别装得不想看似的,布鲁西！
Don't act like you ain't want to see more, Brucie!
- 对,是你想要,朋友 - 不,你是想要我再吻你
- Yeah, you wish, pal. - No, you wish I'd kiss you again,
你的口臭就像八泡鲨鱼屎一样
because your breath smell like eight cans of shark shit.
就是用十英尺长的杆子碰她我都恶心
I wouldn't touch her with a 10-foot pole.
- 他说什么？ - 他是个变态
- What's he talking about? - He's a freak.
跑啊,阿甘,跑啊！ （《阿甘正传》里的台词）
Run, Forrest, run!
白人就是这样弹吉他的
That's how a white man plays guitar.
队长,他说他有些情报
Captain, he said he had some info.
你们在玩“Halo 2”,我以为这还没出呢
You guys have "Halo 2." I didn't even think that was out yet.
正经点 把音乐关了！
Focus. Turn the music off!
好,队长,你知道那些犯人吧？
Yeah, captain. You know them convicts?
他们现在有些很像样的球员了
They're starting to get some serious players.
可是他们最大的威胁是谁？是一个跑锋,麦吉特
But their biggest threat? A running back. Megget.
- 他很棒？ - 他很快
- He's good? - He's fast.
他非常非常快
He's really, really fast.
我是说,他太快了,很快的人在他面前都显得不快了
I mean, he's so fast, he makes fast people look not fast.
我明白了,他很快
I got it, he's fast.
那么现在让我们看看你的速度,快从这里滚出去吧
Now, why don't you show us your speed and get your pyro ass out of here.
是,长官 我这就走,对不起
Yes, sir. Here I go. I'm sorry.
有什么书可推荐吗,囚犯？
Any books you'd recommend, inmate?
没有,长官
No, sir.
我书读得不多
Not much of a reader.
得了,蛆虫,我以前经常看见你在这里读书
Oh, come on, now, maggot. I've seen you in here reading before.
这个活也是你自己要求的,对吗？
You requested this detail. Isn't that right?
不,我只是喜欢清静,长官
No. It's the quiet time I like, sir.
也许你会喜欢看这本书
Maybe you'd like to read this.
（黑人民权运动领袖马尔科姆·X的传记）
这是什么狗屁书？
What the hell kind of bullshit book is that?
这是历史,长官
It's historical. Sir.
为什么他会喜欢看关于一个四眼黑鬼的书？
Now, why would he want to read a book about a four-eyed nigger?
这个词是不是让你不高兴了？黑鬼？
Does the N word offend you, nigger?
没有,长官
No, sir.
对不起
Sorry about that.
帮我捡一下书你不介意吧,小子？
You mind fetching these books for me, boy?
不介意,长官
No, sir.
把它们捡起来,放到桌上
Just pick them up. Put them on the table.
给您
There you go.
你忘了一本
You forgot one.
你肯定很想打我们吧,唔？
Bet you'd like to hit us, huh?
打你们？长官？不
Hit you, sir? No.
你们都是我的朋友
Y'all my friends.
把它们捡起来
Pick these up.
上！
Go!
给我！我这里空了！我这里空了！
Hit me! I'm open! I'm open!
搞什么！我们还有一个星期就要打比赛了
Come on! We got one week before we play that game.
我们现在还是连传球都做不好
We can't complete a pass yet.
- 麦吉特总不能每一次都带球跑 - 我知道,教练
- Megget can't run the ball every play. - I know, coach.
他到底在笑什么？
What the hell is he smiling at?
这比赛最好是光明正大的
This better be on the up and up.
我可以保证
I guarantee it.
那咱们干吧
Let's do this shit.
咱们的邻居来了
There goes the neighborhood.
现在我再也没机会打球了
Now I'll never get to play.
你们看见了吧？你们看见了吧？迪克在此！
Did you see that? Did you see that? The Deac is here!
很好
Nice.
好,我们封住这里,封住这里
Okay, we seal off here, seal off here.
- 汉堡包 - 在
- Cheeseburger. - Yeah.
你要把这家伙放倒@@
You're just gonna chip this guy@@
痛啊
That stings.
没有大汉堡治不了的伤
It's nothing a Quarter Pounder can't fix.
上面有奶酪吗？
With cheese on it?
一！
Hut!
那小子在沙漠里都会得感冒,给你
Man, that boy would catch a cold in the desert. Here you go.
- 看来一切顺利 - 是啊
- Everything's looking up. - Yeah.
还有点小疮疤需要解决
Still got one more pain in the ass to deal with.
好,你们说怎样？要不要来点好球比赛？
All right, what do you say? How about a little best ball?
不要,我讨厌比赛,大家各打各的球吧
No, I hate that bullshit. Everyone play their own damn ball.
我靠,那是保罗·克鲁吗？
Holy shit, is that Paul Crewe?
你们觉得怎样？MVP来亲我的屁股了
How do you like that, boys? The MVP coming to kiss my ass.
那么,你有什么想法,保罗？
So, what's on your mind, Paul?
关于犯人昂格尔的问题
Got a problem with inmate Unger.
- 他是你队里的人吗？ - 我相信他是你队里的人
- Is he on your little squad? - I believe he's on your little squad.
克鲁先生,拍张照片你不介意吧？好吗？
Mr. Crewe, would you mind if we had a picture? Please?
听典狱长的
That's up to the warden.
- 该死,好吧 - 卷过胶卷了,全都准备好了
- Damn it. All right. - Rewound it. Did everything.
- 闪光灯也准备好了 - 用不着闪光灯,现在是大白天
- The flash is ready. - You don't need a flash. It's daylight.
哦,是我不对,我只想拍得好一点
Oh, my bad. I just want a good picture.
要知道,我认为我老婆在跟我结婚前和你上过床
You know, I think you had sex with my wife before I married her.
- 很抱歉 - 啊,才不呢
- Sorry about that. - Oh, hell, no.
假如她漂亮到可以和职业橄榄球选手搞一夜情
If she's hot enough to have a one-nighter with a pro football player,
那我肯定是赚到了
I must be doing all right.
好,咱们来吧
Okay, here we go.
- 恩格尔哈特警长？ - 是,典狱长
- Sergeant Engleheart? - Yes, warden.
到镜头外面去好吗？
Would you step out of the picture, please?
是,长官
Yes, sir.
- 他老婆有最性感的屁股 - 太棒了
- His wife has got the hottest ass. - Great.
咱们还是开门见山吧
Just cut to the chase, shall we?
你其实并没觉得你有机会赢,是吗？
You don't actually think you have a chance of winning, now, do you?
我们跳不出你的手心
We're gonna get our asses handed to us.
我知道,你也知道,我只是不想让我的队员知道
I know it. You know it. I just don't want my players to know it.
你的队员？
Your players?
我还以为我已经把你都摸透了呢
Just when I thought I had you all figured out.
- 这是什么意思？ - 在你进来以后
- What does that mean? - In the time you've been here,
你没有打过或接过一个电话
you haven't made or received one telephone call.
你没有拆过一封信
You haven't opened so much as a single shred of mail.
你怎么会在乎这些混球？
What do you give a damn about those slimeballs?
你这辈子从没关心过任何人
You never cared about anybody in your entire life.
哦,也许我终于找到了
Well, maybe I finally found that sense of family
从小就渴望的家庭温暖
I been yearning for since I'm a baby.
而且对上帝起誓
And gosh almighty,
如果你把昂格尔赶出球场
my new family and l would sure appreciate it
我的新家人和我都会很感激,你听到了吗？
if you got Unger off the field. You hear?
恩格尔哈特警长
Sergeant Engleheart.
谢谢你
Thank you.
哦,至于你的请求@@
Oh, and as for your request@@
@@你很快就会得到我的答复
@@you'll have my answer soon enough.
昨天晚上下雨了？
Did it rain last night?
一滴都没下
Not a drop.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
好吧,小伙子们
All right, boys.
典狱长是想让我们泄气
The warden is trying to break our spirit.
他以为我们今天会放弃训练
He thinks we're gonna skip practice today,
等场地变干,明天再说
wait for the field to dry, make it up tomorrow.
你们知道吗？谁在乎这个？
You know what? Who gives a shit?
离比赛还有三天 我们能对付
Three days till game time. We can handle it.
不过听我说：
But let me say this:
那个拿水浇球场的老头 让我知道了一件事
That old man flooding this field tells me something.
这家伙害怕了
The guy is scared.
害怕你们这些有问题的、堕落的囚犯
Scared of you sick, degenerate convicts.
你们知道吗？
And you know what?
他应该害怕
He should be.
因为我要告诉你们一个消息
Because I got news for you guys.
我们要赢
We're gonna win this thing.
他说了“赢”吗？
Did he say "win"?
现在怎么办,小伙子们？
What's it gonna be, boys?
我们是回到牢房去,就这样过一天？
Do we go back to our cells, call it a day?
还是为了橄榄球历史上 最伟大的造反节日
Or do we get ourselves ready for the greatest ass-kicking fiesta
做准备？
in the history of football?
由你们来决定
I'll leave it up to you guys.
嘿,你也是这混蛋球队的一员
Hey. You're part of the goddamn team.
你这假球分子也去吧
Get your point-shaving ass in there.
说得对
You got it.
我猜海岑那个混蛋在比赛时会使阴招
I guess that asshole Hazen wants to play dirty.
- 我们都是囚犯,对吧？ - 对
- We all convicts, right? - Right.
说不定现在是我们 拿出囚犯样子的时候了
Maybe it's time we started acting like it.
就是这儿,就是这儿
Right here. Right here.
拿着,迪克
Take it, Deac.
咱们看看哪些看守曾经骨折过
Let's see which guards have some broken bones.
耶！
Yeah!
类固醇
雌性激素
鞋子,黑鬼！
Shoes, nigga!
瞧这个,黄铜关节指套 差不多和我一样年纪
Check this out. These be brass knuckles. They damn near old as me.
一！
Hut!
棒极了,汉堡包！ 再好没有了
That's perfect, Cheeseburger! Never been better.
好球,好球
Good ball. Good ball.
好
Okay.
- 我们要揍扁谁？ - 看守们！
- Who we gonna crush? - The guards!
- 我们要宰掉谁？ - 看守们！
- Who we gonna kill? - The guards!
- 我们要亲吻谁？ - 看守们！
- Who we gonna kiss? - The guards!
中招了
Gotcha.
熄灯！
Lights out!
晚安,女士们
Good night, ladies.
- 喂,克鲁！ - 唔,凯尔泰克先生
- Yo, Crewe! - Yes, Mr. Caretaker.
看看你的马桶 里面有给你的 小惊喜
Check your toilet. There should be a little surprise in there for you.
你在我马桶里放了大便？
You took a shit in my toilet?
不是,那是我扔在布鲁西的马桶里的
No, that's the surprise I left in Brucie's toilet.
- 给你的是别的东西 - 好吧
- You got something else. - All right.
哦,瞧瞧这个
Well, would you look at this.
一瓶Ketel One（伏特加酒） 和两个杯子？
A bottle of Ketel One and two glasses?
为什么我需要两个杯子？
Now, what would I need two for?
闭嘴,给我也倒一杯
Just shut up and pour me a drink, bitch.
- 老兄,谁把你教得这么酷的？ - 我妈
- Man, who taught you to be so cool? - My mama.
等我从这儿出去了,我也不要 你把整个好莱坞的人都找来
Now, when I get out of here, I don't want you to get all Hollywood on us.
我只要你和她见一面
I want you to meet her.
给,瞧瞧我的姑娘 她是你的头号崇拜者
Here, look at my girl. She's your biggest fan.
你妈妈很漂亮
Your mom's beautiful.
你嘛,你很丑
And you, you are ugly.
谢谢,我知道了
Thank you. Got it.
这是敬@@
Here's to@@
@@我也不知道是多久以来的 第一个朋友
@@the first friend I've had in I don't know how long.
嘿,我以为我也是你朋友呢,保罗
Hey, I thought I was your friend, Paul.
你是,斯韦托斯基 赶快看完你 那本图画书,睡觉去吧
You are, Switowski. Just finish your coloring book and go back to sleep.
好
Okay.
这个是希望在今后三五年里的什么时候
And here's to having one of these with you on the outside,
和你一起在外面喝一杯
sometime in the next three to five years.
- 喂,克鲁 - 唔,先生
- Yo, Crewe. - Yes, sir.
你以前是橄榄球运动员
You being a ex-football player and all,
在外面肯定有很多漂亮姘头
I'm sure you got a lot of hot ass on the outside.
喂,别忘了,我在外面 还不是最受欢迎的
Well, let's not forget I wasn't the most popular guy out there.
别说这种屁话
Don't give me that shit.
辛普森把他老婆的脑袋都砍掉了 照样能找到姘头
O.J. chopped his wife's head off and still got some ass.
哈哈哈
Yeah.
我妈妈教我不要找了女人还到处 声张 现在睡觉吧
My mama taught me not to kiss and tell. Now, go to sleep.
好吧,我还有一个问题要问你
All right. I got one more question to ask you.
好的,是什么？
Okay. What is it?
为什么你要打假球？
Why'd you shave those points?
你没看报纸吗？ 我是清白的
Didn't you read the papers? I'm innocent.
对 我们大家不都是吗？
Yeah. Ain't we all?
喂,克鲁,要是我帮你 把看守们去年比赛的录像搞来
Yo, Crewe, what would you say
你会怎么说？
if I could get you film from the guards' games last year?
我会说那真神了,可你怎么搞？
I would say that's incredible, but how?
谢谢,先生们
Thanks, gentlemen.
典狱长和他只要15分钟就完事
The warden will be done with him in 15 minutes.
- 我们能对付他 - 是的,太太
- We can handle him. - Yes, ma'am.
那我们走了,太太
Then you're gonna, ma'am.
干得好
Nice job.
我都说不出这对我有多重要 谢谢你,莉奈特
I can't tell you how much this means to me. Thank you, Lynette.
现在内特可以研究看守们的所有阵形了
Now Nate can study all the guards' formations.
别那么快,小糖熊
Not so fast, sugar bear.
你得付报酬
You gotta earn them.
我们只有15分钟
We only got 1 5 minutes,
但是亲爱的,我们不会浪费 每一分钟
but, sunshine, we're gonna make them all count.
再来一杯好吗？
One more, please?
走吧
Let's go.
- 静一静,哥们 - 开始吧
- Quiet down. Guys. - Let's go.
在看看守们去年的比赛录像之前
Before we watch the guards' game film from last season,
我们的保罗·克鲁先生 要给大家送上一个特别节目
we have a special presentation from our very own Mr. Paul Crewe.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
怎么回事？
What's going on?
我又要再体验一遍这个？
Now I gotta relive this shit?
好耶
Yeah!
你可以说,我的朋友很会配合！
You can say this, my man's a team player!
你知道他们怎么说：你一旦变老 就没有别的路了！
You know what they say. Once you go gray, there ain't no other way!
嘿,嘿,嘿,布鲁西！布鲁西！ 你觉得这个好玩,我很高兴
Hey, hey, hey. Brucie! Brucie! I'm glad you think that's funny,
因为我有些很好玩的东西给你们看
because I got something pretty funny to show you guys.
托尼,来吧 你们会喜欢的
Tony, hit it. You're gonna like this.
（洗衣间）
- 这到底是什么？ - 什么？很好啊,继续
- What the hell is this? - What? It's good. It keeps going.
- 嗨 - 我在这儿
- Hi. - Here I am.
关掉,关掉
Turn this shit off. Turn it off.
不行！
No!
对,对,对 很好玩 这是特技做出来的
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Very funny. Trick photography.
没发生什么事 没发生什么事
Nothing happened. Nothing happened.
我是在表演摔跤,就这么回事
I was showing a little wrestling move. That's all.
暂停！
Knock it off!
趁着看守还没回来
It's time we took a look at what we came here to see
我们该看看正经东西了
before the guards come back.
第一个录像是看守队 对德克萨斯南方队的进攻
The first film is the guards' offense against Texas Southern.
你们可以看到 他们用的是标准的叉骨阵形
Now, as you can see, they're running a standard wishbone.
你是说这些畜牲在看我们的比赛录像
So you're telling me that these animals are watching our game films.
- 对吗？ - 是的,老大
- Is that right? - Yes, sir, boss.
上赛季的比赛他们全搞到了
They got all last season.
看来我们应该有所行动
Seems to me that we ought to do something about this.
你要我干什么？
What do you want me to do?
你是罪犯 发挥想象力吧
You're the criminal. Be creative.
不过在比赛那天,假如我这么--
But on game day, if I so much as--
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
我不知道 我身上老是发热
I don't know. I've had hot flashes all shift,
现在我的乳头又让我难过得要命
and now my nipples are killing me.
我们干吗要关心你的乳头？
Why are we talking about your nipples?
不用 接着做你的事吧
We're not. Just go do what you're doing there.
哥们
Guys.
我要让克鲁完蛋
I want Crewe finished.
是,长官 你给了我灵感,长官 我有办法对付他
Yes, sir. You give me the inspiration, sir. I got something for him.
一！
Hut!
各位！
Everybody!
集合！
Huddle up!
我们天天受罪,已经熬了很久
Every day we've been taking shit, for a long time.
明天,就要报仇 现在,稍微想一想吧
Tomorrow, payback. Now, think about that for a second.
- 什么时候？ - 比赛时候！
- What time is it? - Game time!
明天12:00,公车就会走,别迟到了！
Tomorrow, 1 2:00, the bus leaves. Don't be late!
凯尔泰克到底在哪儿？
Where the hell is Caretaker?
不知道
I don't know.
给你的礼物,克鲁先生
A gift for you, Mr. Crewe.
他怎么听这种狗屁玩意？
How does he listen to that cracker shit?
我们现在是在一片不毛之地的中心
We're here deep in the heart of toothless country,
从一个简陋的德克萨斯 高中体育馆向您直播
coming to you from a simple Texas high school stadium
这个体育馆已经为一件大事而作了翻新
that's been retrofitted for the big event.
当我的同事特拉维斯把我拖到 这里来的时候,我说：
Now, when my man T ravis tried to drag me out here, I said,
“你怎么回事？对袭击者队的球迷 采访太多,脑子坏掉了吗？
"What are you, brain-dead from talking to too many Raider fans?
这里不能做节目的 ”
It's not going to work."
但事实是,这里可能将发生 载入史册的大事
But the fact of the matter is, this could shape up as an epic day.
热狗摊主、大威力步枪 我喜欢这种组合
Hot-dog vendors, high-powered rifles, I love the combination.
并且球迷也如此疯狂
And apparently so do the fans.
嗨！猪头们！
Hey, shitheads! Listen up!
立正！典狱长要讲话
Everybody on their feet for the warden.
安东尼,你还是坐着吧
Anthony, wow. You can sit down.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
先生们,得克萨斯州警方 很友善的
Gentlemen, Texas marshals have been kind enough
为我们提供了十二个神枪手
to supply us with a dozen of their finest sharpshooters.
你们如果想趁乱混到人群中
So for those of you thinking of mingling with the civilians
或者是想逃走
or trying to make a break for it,
就等着吃子弹吧
you will be shot.
子弹会正中头部
In the head.
让我们出去运动吧
Now, let's all go out there and have some fun!
克鲁！赛场见
Crewe! I'll see you on the field!
我觉得他爱上你了
I think he's in love with you.
好了,大家听着
All right, listen up.
我知道凯尔退克不在这儿 大家很难鼓足士气
I know it's hard to get psyched for the game without Caretaker being here.
但是这个小东西
But somehow that sick, skinny bastard
在阴间也会给我们打气
found a way to get us all fired up from beyond the grave.
凯尔退克给我们的最后礼物
Caretaker's last gift to us.
班涛,我觉得这个是给你的
Battle, I presume this is yours.
我觉得还不够大
I still don't think that's big enough.
- 就这些？ - 不是,还有
- That's it? - No, that ain't it.
凯尔泰克说过他会弄些 适合我们穿的
Caretaker said he'd find us some gear to wear.
而且他把我们的名字也 弄上去了
I think he found us a name too.
邪恶战车！邪恶战车！ 邪恶战车！
Mean Machine! Mean Machine! Mean Machine! Mean Machine!
下午好,欢迎收看ESPN体育台 这场特殊的橄榄球赛
Good afternoon and welcome to a very special edition of ESPN football.
今天比赛将在来自阿伦维尔联邦监狱 狱警组成的半职业球队
As today, the semipro Allenville Federal Prison guards
与他们所看守的犯人之间展开
will be taking on the very prisoners they guard.
这个特殊的比赛当然 也由特殊的主持人来播报
And with this special game, folks, comes a special broadcast,
所以我和娃娃脸鲍勃 一起来到这个播音间
as I'm joined in the booth by Baby Face Bob.
跟大家问个好,鲍勃
Say hi to the folks, Bob-O.
克里斯,插入广告
Chris, we went to a commercial.
节目过程中 我们应该互相交换意见
This job, Bob, it's a lot of give and take.
所以我把话题转给你的时候 大胆的对听众说吧说吧
So when I bring you in, don't be afraid to talk to the folks.
除非你不原意
Unless you don't want to.
现在出场的是囚犯队
And here come the cons,
领队是前美国橄榄球协会最有价值 球员四分卫保罗克鲁
Ied by former NFL MVP quarterback Paul Crewe.
天啊！！乖乖！
Holy shit. Hey, hey, hey.
嗨！你们好！
Well, hello. How are you?
离姑娘们远点！
Back away from the girls!
- 快点 - 给我打电话！
- Hey, now. - Call me!
你怎么也穿成这样？
What the hell are you dressed up for?
你以为我花14年呆在监狱 只是为了看看比赛？
Hey, I didn't spend 14 years in the joint just to watch this game.
那边是高度警戒的露天看台
And there in the high-security bleachers
以及举止端庄的囚犯
are the good-behavior cons, along with their@@
还有……貌似拉拉队员……
@@cheerleaders?
我们是邪恶战车
We're the mean machine Don't mean to dis you
我们要打败你 然后给你香吻
We're gonna kick your ass And then we'll kiss you
嗨嗨哈一！
Hey! Ho! What?
不是我干的
I didn't do it!
Come on, Batt!
- 快看 - 怎么回事？
- What's that? - Did you see that?
真见鬼
Damn it!
帕约翰正在二十码处,十码了 他要得分了
Papajohn's at the 20, the 10. And he will score.
做个美梦吧！贱种
Sweet dreams, bitch.
这是一次90码的回攻
That's a 90-yard return.
说句老实话我觉得 囚犯似乎更喜欢打狱警
And I gotta tell you, the cons seem more interested in hitting the guards
而不是擒抱的方式来 阻止对方前进
than tackling the ball carrier.
嗨！老妈,老爸 谢谢你们把我从学校接回来
Hey, Mom. Hey, Dad. Thanks for picking me up from school.
今天最大的新闻是
And here comes the big story of the day.
保罗克鲁 正在他的三年服刑期内
Paul Crewe, serving a three-year sentence,
这是他六年前被美国橄榄球协会 禁赛以来第一次正式出席比赛
hasn't played since he was banned from the NFL six years ago.
中位,换位
Center, shift it! Shift it!
嗨！大脚怪兽
Hey, Sasquatch!
20码,一！
Twenty, hut!
克鲁背传 特里没有及时防卫
Crewe drops back to pass. Turley's leaving him unprotected.
失球
Fumble!
妈的
Holy shit!
真见鬼
Goddamn it.
这个大家伙要吃记侵人犯规了
That's gonna be a personal foul on the big guy.
囚犯队真是出师不利
And this is certainly an inauspicious start for the cons.
好了,你摆平他了 现在好好坐我的后卫
Come here! All right! You got him. Now, protect me!
我们上！压倒他们
Let's go! Hold them!
现在的形势是科纳瓦和 狱警进攻小队
And here comes Knauer and that big offensive unit for the guards.
八十六
Eighty-six.
回你的笼子去
Back to your cell.
一！二！
Hut! Hut!
囚犯们的后防空虚 狱警得分
Knauer has Potter wide open. Touchdown, guards.
仅在开场90秒
- Son of a bitch! - And in the first 90 seconds,
狱警的比分扶摇直上 因为两个攻方持球得分（各6分）
the guards are up by two touchdowns.
看上去这个比赛会速战速决
This one looks like it could be over early.
抱歉
Sorry.
你们高兴什么？ 这是14：0的大比分
What are we celebrating for?! It's 1 4-nothing!
你们要真想摆平那些混蛋 应该在记分板上体现
You guys wanna beat these assholes, do it on the scoreboard!
你没事吧？ 天啊,你受伤了？
Are you okay? Oh, God, you're not hurt, are you?
你怎么婆婆妈妈的！
Jesus, you sound like my mother.
你要是想哭就尽情地哭吧 我会陪着你哭的
Listen, if you wanna cry, you go ahead and cry. I'll cry with you.
滚开,回赛场上去 好好教训他们
Get off me! Get back out there and kick some ass!
你怎么对我大喊大叫的？ 我只是关心你
Why are you yelling at me? All I did was care!
打断腿可以医好
Look! A broken leg will heal.
但是如果邪恶战车输了 那将是永久的耻辱
A loss to the Mean Machine lasts forever.
对不起,伙计们
Sorry, guys.
我也很抱歉
Yeah, yeah. Me too.
好了,我们重新开始
All right. Now, let's get started!
上场要给他们点颜色
Now, get the hell out there! Let's go!
这边,这边
Way to go! Way to go!
这可是囚犯队有史以来 第一次出现的好迹象
There's the first sign of life from the cons.
看看克鲁小丑能做点什么名堂
Let's see if Paul "Motley" Crewe can make something happen.
一！
Hut!
克鲁要丢球了 他找到迪肯的空当
On first down, Crewe will throw. He's got Deacon wide open.
这个应该是犯规
That's gotta be pass interference.
但是裁判示意没事
But the ref is waving it off.
怎么回事?
- What?! - Oh, come on!
这件事可太不让人舒适
Come on, now. I'm in this hellhole for less than that.
- 像个男人那样公正判罚 - 没问题
- Be a man and make a call. - You're right.
黑队88号！无体育道德
Unsportsmanlike conduct! Eighty-eight black!
什么？
What?!
好了
Come on!
真是垃圾！
This is baby-back bullshit!
冷静,我们继续
- Bullshit, D. - Calm down. Let it go.
这个可真是个可以的判罚
Let's call that one a questionable call.
蓝色42方案
Blue 42, hut!
球传给了麦吉特,他转身到外围 位置不错
The give is to Megget. He spins to the outside. Megget has room.
他到了35码区,40码区
He's at the 35. The 40.
他被人拽倒了 拽的是头盔
He's brought down hard, by his facemask.
你看到了吗？ 他拽拉我的头盔
What? Oh, come on, man! That was a facemask!
- 这个你也不判罚？ - 我觉得这个正当防守
- You're not gonna call that? - I saw a clean tackle, sir.
你是干什么的？ 你真的这么想？
What you looking at? Are you serious?
去你和你的假释审批官争论吧 你这个罪犯
Tell it to the parole board, criminal.
这可太荒唐了
I mean, this is absurd.
我们遇到这种裁判员 根本没有赢的机会
We can't win with the refs on the payroll!
我有办法了
Listen up. I got an idea to end all this bullshit.
来大家振作
Come on, let's all stay up! Come on!
就位
Down, set!
红队58
Red 58.
掩护你的人
Cover your man!
红队58
Red 58. Hut!
这一计可够他受的
That one hurt my marble sack.
好了
All right!
- 你怎么样？ - 没事
- You all right? - Yeah.
- 现在该第几次进攻？ - 第五次
- What down is it? - Fifth.
- 算第四次吧 - 好的
- No, no. It would be fourth down. - Okay.
他好像在说：“我的‘球’啊”
你觉得怎么样？ 我这次是不是该左路进攻？
What do you think? Should I go for the left nut this time?
向下！开球吧
Underneath! Let's go!
裁判你挡着比赛了 你在这个位置比较好
Ref, you gotta get in the game! Right over here!
我不太清楚, 但是就现在的进攻形势,囚犯队任务艰巨
Well, I don't quite get this, but on fourth and 22, the cons are gonna go for it.
进攻,就位
Down, set!
红队58
Red 58.
Red 58. Hut!
你可得保护好你那“小棒球”
You gotta always protect the McNuggets.
从现在开始, 你公平判罚怎么样？
How about from now on, you call a fair game? How's that sound?
好吧
Sounds good.
不错,润润
Okay. Wet Willie.
我知道你喜欢
Yeah, you like that.
在看过这么一系列荒诞的进攻后
And so the guards will take over
现在轮到狱警队来进攻了
after one of the strangest offensive series I've ever seen.
大家都熟悉战场上的情况了吧
Okay, boys. We know who doesn't have any balls out there now.
我们有信心吗？
Have we got any? Have we got some balls?
- 当然！ - 去吧！打垮他们
- Yeah! - All right! Let's go kick some ass!
斯韦托就位
Come on, Swit, stand them up, baby.
白队50注意
White 50. White 50. Hut, hut, hut!
科纳瓦,行动迅速 带给我们场闪电战
Knauer, play action. Here comes the blitz.
斯韦托斯基真是个大块 他的擒抱防卫看上去就像有腿的可乐售货机
Switowski is so big, it's like being tackled by a Coke machine with legs.
真是有趣
This is fun!
很高兴看到你笑,鲍勃
Nice to see you smiling, Bob.
谢谢,克里斯
Thanks, Chris.
直达90码
Green 90! Hut!
球传给了麦吉特
Third and 5, and the give is to Megget.
他到了40码线 进攻看来停下了
He's to the 40, where he'll come up short.
但是特利想法向前推进
But look at Turley push the pile.
克鲁也上了
And now Crewe.
第一次进攻结束
And that's a first down!
场上情形进入白热化 要是没人来控制
And look out. Boy, somebody better take control of this game soon,
我看要出人命了
or they're gonna need body bags on the sidelines.
来吧,伙计们
Let's go, guys.
第二次四分之一进攻开始
Start of the second quarter.
虽然囚犯队失利两次 但是显然他们并没有失去势头
Cons still down by two touchdowns, but they finally have some momentum.
Hut!
克鲁把球急传给了麦吉特
Crewe with a shovel pass to Megget.
麦吉特的进攻结束
And Megget scrambles for a first down.
你跟我耍花招
Oh, you fooled me.
- 你种着了吧 - 是啊
- I got you there, didn't l? - You did.
恩格尔哈特你是 你队友里长得最好看的一个
You know, Engleheart, you are the best-looking guy on your team.
保罗你是这些人中 第一个对我说这些……
You know, Paul, in the midst of all this, for you to say something like that is@@
来吧来吧,继续防守
Come on, let's go. Let's go, D.
这次进攻从35码起
First and 10 at the guards' 35.
克鲁把球中传给了迪肯莫斯
Crewe dumps it over the middle to Deacon Moss.
而他继续将战线推进了13码
And he's hammered at the 17 for a 13-yard pickup, and that's a first down.
克鲁正极力
- 一！
Hut! - Crewe, trying to get his team
刷新比分
on the scoreboard.
他掷出了
He will throw.
迪肯莫斯接住了 而且得分
And it's caught by Deacon Moss for a touchdown!
太好啦！
All right!
好了他们今天终于有幸 出现在比分牌上了
And so there'll be no shutout today, as the cons are on the board.
别叹息了 我们两队都尽力打比赛呢
Quit booing, people. Both teams are trying very hard!
你是怎么回事？ 别把自己当成是啦啦队长
What the hell's wrong with you? Stop acting like a damn cheerleader!
- 这是运动员精神,你也试试？ - 闭嘴
- Sportsmanship, try it. - Shut up.
Damn.
比分2：1上半时还剩一分钟 丹哈姆现在是后卫
2:1 1 left in the first half. And Dunham is back in at fullback.
真是重磅出击 他6英尺2英寸260磅
And he is a load, at 6'2", 260.
丹哈姆 突破了对手的擒抱
Dunham, breaking tackles.
他继续进攻
He refuses to go down.
最后还是在15码处倒地
But he finally does after a 1 5-yard gain.
你知道为什么只有 白人可以玩转橄榄球吗?
That's how a white man runs a football.
如果是我在防守 我会让你更难看
If I was on D, I'd crack you square in that egg-ass head of yours.
但是你不是防守队员 小贱货
Yeah, but you ain't on D. Are you, bitch?
斯韦托斯基！过来
Switowski! Come here.
你知道那个坏蛋 在图书馆怎么说我？
Do you know what he said to me in the library?
没错,让他出局
Yes. Him. Out.
防守防守
D, D, defense D, D, defense
看来囚犯队还是没有对抗 丹哈姆的良策
The cons don't seem to have an answer for Dunham,
谁能轻易拉平12比分呢
who's averaging close to 12 yards a carry this half.
突进67
Green 67.
Green 67. Hut!
丹哈姆不敌斯韦托斯基
Oh, what a hit on Dunham by Switowski.
我觉得我摆平他了
I think I made him shit himself.
我觉得他被摆平了
- Shit! - I think he just shit himself.
I think he just shit himself.
天啊 摆平他可真不容易
Good Lord. This guy shit himself bigtime.
哈一！是我摆平他的
See? I told you I made him shit himself!
我会去医院送书给他的
Yo! I'll make sure I send them books to the hospital, pimp.
还有尿布
And some diapers.
还有19秒 这里有很多草皮
Nineteen seconds. We got a lot of ground to cover.
你们还记得我们 在泥浆上的训练吗？
So you bastards remember that play we practiced in the mud?
泥浆？ 这里是正规的赛场！
What are you talking about? That was some schoolyard bullshit.
那我们就玩点赛场把戏
Yeah. Let's try some schoolyard bullshit.
来吧,防守
Come on, D, let's go.
进攻吧88号
Down, set! Green 88.
Green 88. Hut!
时钟开始运转,克鲁把球传给了麦吉特 是反方向的
The clock starts to run. Crewe hands the ball to Megget. It's a reverse.
汉堡包埃迪拿到了球
Cheeseburger Eddy's got it.
前进吧
Go, baby, go!
他侧传给迪肯
He laterals to Deacon.
阻止他！
T ackle him!
传给特里
To Turley.
时钟继续运转 球传给了布鲁西
The clock is running. To Brucie.
又给了卡尔-斯坦福
Shades of Cal-Stanford.
又回到克鲁手里
Back to Crewe.
他掷给麦吉特
He tosses to Megget.
阻止他
T ackle him!
看看小麦吉特跑起来的样子
And look at that little Megget run.
还剩3秒了
Three seconds left.
加油吧！
Yeah! Go!
没人拦得住他,得分
He could go all the way. Touchdown!
你们看到了吧？！
Did you see that?!
在那样叫一下
Do that sound again.
我很喜欢
I like that.
这可真是奇迹般的比赛
And so, on a miraculous play,
囚犯队在上半场扳平比分 14平
the cons end the first half with the score: 14-all.
注意！
Bring it in.
你们知道你们要输给谁？
Do you have any idea who's beating you out there?
这肯定是爆炸新闻
This was supposed to be a blowout,
而且整个国家的人都在看着我们
and they're showing you up in front of the whole nation.
整个国家
The whole nation!
我喜欢他生气的样子
I like it when he's angry.
- 我跟你说了！ - 这边走
- I told you! - Way to go, baby, way to go.
你觉得你在做什么？
What in the hell do you think you're doing out there?
打比赛！
Playing football, sir.
我可没说让你赢
I didn't say nothing about winning.
我们没赢,至少现在
We're not winning. Not yet.
你这个给自己找麻烦 克鲁先生
You got yourself in quite a predicament, Mr. Crewe.
- 是吗？ - 听好了
- Is that right? - See, it's just come to my attention
昂格尔已经因为谋杀凯尔泰克
that inmate Unger has been taken into custody
被特殊监管了
for the murder of Caretaker.
- 很好 - 是的,是件好事
- Good. - Oh, yeah, it's good.
还有件事,他说他有个同伙
Only thing is, he claims to have an accomplice.
他说是你是合谋
Claims you knew all about it.
而且他说是你让凯尔泰克 去你的牢房的
Hell, he even says you sent Caretaker to your cell.
胡说八道
Bullshit.
科纳瓦上尉说他看到你和昂格尔 共同策划整个事件
Captain Knauer says he saw you planning it with Unger.
这些成不了法庭的证据
There's no way that could hold up in court.
法庭？
Court?
小子！在阿伦维尔会有法律？ 一切都是我说了算
Hell, boy, in Allenville, I'm the judge, I'm the jury,
而且鉴于你的特殊情况 我还可以为你执行死刑
and in your particular case, I'm the executioner.
你要怎么样？
What do you want?
我要你输了比赛
I want you to lose.
我做不到
I can't do that.
你当然可以 而且,你很有经验
Of course you can. After all, you've had plenty of practice.
但是你要知道 输赢对他们来说更重要
But the men. It's more important to them than it is to you.
没关系,你自己选择
Okay. Suit yourself.
就在监狱里继续碌碌无为的 待个25年怎么样
Spend the next 25 years of your useless life in prison.
好吧,我同意
All right, I'll do it.
但是不要伤害我的人 你们赢了就行了好吗?
But I don't want my guys hurt. You get ahead, you coast. We clear?
没问题,我要领先两个 攻方持球触地分
Fine. Right after I get a two-touchdown lead.
我告诉你什么最困扰我 典狱长
I tell you what bothers me the most, warden.
我担心你到了外边以后
That you're not gonna be out there on that field with us,
可能得不到你想要的
getting what you got coming to you.
胜利会属于我
The only thing coming to me is victory.
邪恶战车
Mean Machine.
不错的名字
It's cute.
-我们走吧 - 我们会赢的
- Let's go, boy! - We can do it, baby!
上尉
Captain.
你给我保证吗？
May I have a word?
别担心,典狱长 我们会尽力的
Don't worry, warden, we'll take care of business.
我已经稳操胜卷
I already have.
我们可以自己打赢的
What? We can win this on our own.
上尉,我不会听天由命的
Captain, a man in my position doesn't leave things to chance.
听着,等你领先3个触地得分后
Now, after you get a comfortable three-touchdown lead,
我希望你们继续猛打
I want you to inflict as much pain as humanly possible.
可别放松明白吗？
Do not let up, you hear?
我要让这些囚犯知道谁说了算！
I want those cons to understand who owns them.
我说的清楚吗？
Do I make myself clear?
是的先生！
Oh, yes, sir.
很好
Good.
下半场要开球了
There's the kickoff, and we're under way in the second half.
麦吉特最终在对方33码处被断下
Megget is finally brought down at the guards' 33,
保罗克鲁在这里接替他
where Paul Crewe will take over.
以及上半时战果
And what a first half he's had.
大家加油啊
Here we go! Here we go!
进攻！就位
Down, set!
45码！
Y 45. Hut!
克鲁过了第一个10码
On first and 10, Crewe will pass.
他找到迪肯的空当
- He's got Deacon wide open. - Come on.
失败了
Oh, incomplete.
没关系,继续努力
It's okay. Get your head up.
没关系
It's all right, man.
来吧,泡利
Come on, Paulie.
第二轮,克鲁依旧期待 从迪肯处进攻
Second and 10 from the 33. Crewe's looking for Deacon once again.
他那又空当
- He's open! - He's open!
但是扔过了 被帕约翰接住了
But overthrows it. And it's picked off by Papajohn.
看着,他反攻了
Look out! He might go.
说再见
Say goodbye.
得分
Touchdown!
今天克鲁犯的第一个错误
The first mistake Crewe's made all day.
没关系的 我们会追回来
Short memory, baby. We'll get it back. We'll get it back.
防御！
Defense, let's do this!
上午8：38,第三次进攻
8:38 left in the third quarter,
克鲁正在为后半时努力
and Crewe has struggled thus far in the second half.
Hut!
把球扔给麦吉特 天啊,又失手了
The pitch to Megget. Oh, my! That ball is live!
被兰伯特捡到
It's picked up by Lambert.
他在15码处,10码 得分在望
He's at the 1 5, the 1 0, and he will score!
得分！！
Yeah! T ouchdown! Yeah!
克鲁摔倒了很慢的爬起来
Crewe took a shot on that play and he's getting up slowly.
于此同时,狱警队在边场庆祝
Meanwhile, in the end zone, the guards have something to celebrate,
庆祝他们连续两个 越过对方球门线的六分
as they find themselves up by two touchdowns.
后半场的保罗克鲁 可真是发挥失常
This is simply a different Paul Crewe we're seeing here in the second half.
保罗克鲁老矣 这么写吧
There's the old Paul Crewe we love to write about.
你在赛场上怎么回事？
What the hell are you doing out there?
我不行了
I'm done.
我完了,就是这样
I'm out. That's it.
- 你哪受伤了？ - 膝盖
- Where you hurting? - My knee.
- 我觉得没事 - 是的
- Seems okay to me. - Well, it ain't.
如果保罗不上场 谁来做四分卫？
If Crewe can't go, I don't know how deep these guys are at quarterback.
狱警队将尽力防卫麦吉特
The guards will try to keep it away from Megget, so they'll pooch kick.
完美的接球
Fair catch. Fair catch.
大东尼正为完美接球叫喊
As Big Tony calls for the fair catch.
看看,这是有史以来最慢的撞击
Watch out. That was as late a hit as I've ever seen.
而且人们看上去很不欣赏这个
And even some of the home crowd not liking that one.
伙伴,撑着点
Hang in there, partner.
玉米罐,玉米罐 我没事的
Can of corn. Can of corn, and I'll be fine. Can of corn.
我也不好过
Yeah, I'd have a hard time looking at me too.
布鲁西
Brucie.
在这,教练
Yeah, coach.
这种进攻最适合你了,上吧
You're the only one that knows this offense, son. Now, do it.
替换受伤的保罗克鲁的人是
Coming into the game, replacing the injured Paul Crewe,
1号,布鲁西
is number 1, Brucie.
好了来吧 克鲁打的太烂了
All right, all right. Crewe's playing like shit.
那时他自己的问题 我来了形势会好转的
That's his problem. I'm gonna bring us back.
我们来个鹞子翻身
Right, 32 Flex Dive Motion on one. Ready!
来吧
Break!
现在是布鲁西时刻
Yeah. It's Brucie's time to shine, baby.
来吧,进攻
Okay. Down, set. Hut!
又一次失球 但是狱警们很快扑了上去
There's the snap and the ball is fumbled. And the guards recover.
我不该吃那些爆米花
I knew I shouldn't have had that popcorn.
现在狱警们在场上占主导地位
The guards are in command here as we move late into the third quarter.
来吧九十八
Ninety-eight. 一！二！
一！
Hut! Hut!
球传给了鲍特 又回传给科纳瓦
The give is to Potter. Back to Knauer.
他在前场的到一个优势进攻位置
He's got a man open deep downfield.
一个交替传球
He'll throw the flea-flicker!
接得很准,得分 狱警队
And he's got it. Touchdown, guards.
看起来比分开始失控了
And this game is starting to look like a blowout.
这就是你对 凯尔泰克的回报？
Hey, man, after all Caretaker did, this is how you show him love?
别担心
Don't worry about it.
你一点也没变
You haven't changed one damn bit.
好了,来吧！
All right. Down, set!
布鲁西继续担任四分卫
Back in at quarterback is Brucie,
看看这次会把球传给谁
who will try to find a handle on the ball this time.
扔出去,布鲁西
Throw it, Brucie!
真糟
Oh, shit!
留神看
And look out.
重重一击！
What a shot he took!
你还要我们损失多少？
How much more blood do you want?
我觉得囚犯队选错了四分卫
I think the cons are just about out of options at quarterback.
斯基奇 我有个问题要问你
Hey, Skitchy, let me ask you something.
你打了典狱长,你觉得值吗？
When you popped the warden, was it worth it?
值得把你后半身都搭在监狱吗？
Was it worth spending the rest of your life in here?
当然值,每一秒都值得
Was it worth it? It was worth every goddamn second.
他想怎么样？
What the hell is he doing?
保罗克鲁应该感觉好多了 因为他又上场
Paul Crewe must be feeling better, because here he comes.
好了我想你们 所以我上场了
All right, I missed you guys, so I'm back.
我想我们要做很多才能赶上
We got a lot of work to do. Let's get it going.
89码处来个袭击,行吗？
Deuce right, 89. Fly on two. Ready?
很好！
Break.
第四轮进攻囚犯队已经落后 3个六分球
As we start the fourth quarter, cons down by three touchdowns.
左边注意
Wide left! Tight left!
直捣90码！
Black 90. 一！二！
一！
Hut! Hut!
又一个闪电战！
Here comes the blitz, and no one's blocking!
克鲁被困在其中
And Crewe will be sacked for a big loss.
看上去又是克鲁进攻的信息
That looked like a message to Crewe from his offensive line.
你们看到了 有个空当
Did you see that, man? They're quitting on him.
来吧！还是闪电战术
Okay, baby. Jailbreak Blitz. Ready?
这是我应得的
We got that out of the way. I deserved it.
- 让他们知道什么是橄榄球 - 换位
- Now we gotta play some football. - Switch it! Switch it!
囚犯队得很努力才能 改变劣势
Cons need to do something to get back in this game.
可不是这样
And that's not it!
克鲁已经被瞄准
And Crewe is leveled!
我觉得他可能爬不起来了
I don't think he's gonna get up from that one.
不错的撞击
Nice hit!
但是他还是爬了起来 真不知道他是怎么做到的
But he is. And I don't know how, after that last hit.
来次弃踢吧
All right, punt team!
让他们比较远的地方开始 没问题吧
Keep them off the field! We're going for it.
傻蛋菜会这么做 行动起来
Dumbshits are going for it! Let's go! Let's go!
回来吧,如果他想挨打
Come on back, if he wants to get his ass kicked. Come on back.
简直太不可思议了
This is unbelievable.
你们要是不想和我合作 我就自己来
Fine. You guys don't wanna help me, I'll do it on my own. On two.
去界限上
Let's go, to the line.
在20码线上
On fourth and 20,
囚犯队决定做一次努力 这才像是正式比赛
the cons are gonna go for it. This could be the ball game right here.
红队98注意
Red 98. 一！二！
一！
Hut! Hut!
克鲁劈开了闪电战术 但是掉了他的头盔
Crewe dodges the blitz, but he loses his helmet.
他继续前进
And he's not going down.
不错的战果
He's got the first down.
暂停
Time-out!
- 这才是男人 - 不错啊
- Man, oh, man. - Not bad.
集合
Huddle up.
听着
Look.
我知道你们都猜到了 但是我还是要大声说出来
I'm sure you already know this, but I never said it out loud.
我放弃这次比赛了
I did throw that game.
刚才是这样
I did it.
我被坏人威胁
I was in a bad way with some worse people.
我这样做的时候
After I did it,
我感觉糟透了 我觉得不如让人杀了我算了
I felt so shitty I wish I would have just let them kill me instead.
典狱长会要挟要我将 如果我不放弃这次比赛
Now the warden wants to pin Caretaker's murder on me
他要将谋杀凯尔泰克 的罪责加于我
if I don't throw this game.
看起来我们还可以相处更长时间
So it looks like I'm gonna get to know you guys a lot better,
因为我不会两次犯同一错误
because I ain't doing that twice in a lifetime.
时间所剩不多 但是我们还可以挽回局面
We got a little time left. We can still do this.
我请求你们 把手放在这里
I'm begging you. Put your hands in here.
谢谢你们 我们是谁？
Okay. Thank you. Now, who are we?
邪恶战车
Mean Machine!
来吧！邪恶战车！
Come on, Mean Machine, let's go!
很高兴你归队了
I'm glad you got back.
这样不用我宰了你了
It doesn't use me to kill you.
真是个好消息
That's great news.
这次有赛的了
All right. We got ourselves a game.
棕色65
Brown 65. Hut!
第一次从10码到30码 克鲁找到迪肯德空当
First and 10 from the 30. Crewe finds Deacon open in the flat.
一！
Hut!
传球给麦吉特 他又使战线向前推进了9码
The give is to Megget. And he fights his way for a 9-yard gain.
一码,再来一码
One yard, baby. One more yard.
一！二！
一！
Hut! Hut!
看克鲁在耍什么小把戏
Crewe tries a sneak. Or is it?
他把球传给麦吉特
He flips it back to Megget.
麦吉特又在继续推进战线
Megget's got the first down and more.
麦吉特这次前进了4码 得分在望
And Megget is down to the 4-yard line, where it'll be first and goal.
一！
Hut!
克鲁传球给特里 看这大家伙怎么做
Crewe hands it to Turley. And look at the big man go.
抱擒阻止他
T ackle him!
得分！
Touchdown!
这里有不少兵乓声
That was some rumbling, bumbling stumbling right there.
听听人群的欢呼吧
And listen to the crowd
观众们也开始喜欢囚犯队
as this underdog con team is starting to win them over.
现在狱警队在29码线上持球
Third down and 6. Guards have the ball on their own 29-yard line.
科纳瓦需要一击获胜
Knauer needs a first down to put this game away.
白队50
White 50!
看看赛场上发生了什么
And look at Battle take off.
他把球打飞了
He knocks the ball loose!
这可真是成堆了 裁判员都有点糊涂了
There's a dogpile in the backfield. The refs are trying to sort it out.
我的胳膊！
My arm!
囚犯队重夺进攻权
The cons recover!
我们抢到了球
We got the ball! We got the ball! We got it! We got it!
剩下的这两分多钟 好像才真正进入比赛
With just over two minutes left to be played, this has turned into a game.
克鲁在25码处开始新的进攻
Crewe will start in great field position at the guards' 25.
看场上的形势 狱警们好像很困惑
And look at this formation. The guards, they're confused.
快移过去
Shift over! Move!
他们想叫暂停 但是来不及了
They're trying to call time-out, but there's the snap.
莫斯被抛在人墙之后 我可不想被这样的墙撞上
Moss is behind a wall of cons. I wouldn't wanna be in front of that thing.
他们要得分了
And they'll score!
- 这样合法吗？ - 是的
- Hey! Is that legal? - Yeah, it is.
- 这样得分了？ - 是的
- Is that a touchdown? - Yes, it is.
到底怎么回事？
What is going on here? Shit!
加上额外的加分 囚犯队只落后7分
And with the extra point, the cons are down by just seven.
- 布鲁西 - 在这呢,教练
- Brucie! - Yeah. Yeah, coach.
沃要你去中线开球
I want you to go out there and kick off.
- 没问题 - 开球
- I can do it. - Kick off!
他跟本就开不好
Brucie can't kick worth a shit.
我知道,去夺球
I know. Recover the ball.
耶稣基督,我的救世主 如果你助我一臂之力
Jesus Christ, my savior. If you help me out with this one,
我保证不再和那个黑人做 对不起我老婆的事了,阿门
I promise to stop cheating on my wife with black guys. Amen.
重返赛场的布鲁西 对这次机会格外珍惜
Back in the game is Brucie, and he'll do the honors.
开球开的太糟糕了
And it's a horrible kick.
但是球还是跌撞着出去了
But the ball is tipped!
而且囚犯队持球
And the cons have come up with it!
真不错,来一次暂停
- We got it! One time-out. - Got it. Got it.
这才是布鲁西 乖乖!
That's it, Brucie. Hey, hey! My bad. My bad. My bad. Come on.
给我
Give me that.
真见鬼
Damn--
没必要这样吧
Well, that felt unnecessary.
囚犯队还有足够的时间 扭转局势
Cons have enough time for one final drive.
克鲁在压力下后传
Crewe drops back to pass. He's under pressure.
- 盯住 - 他在找迪肯
- Watch the pass! - He's looking for Deacon.
他接住了球 但是被防守队员擒抱
He gets the ball up, but he's leveled.
第一次进攻结束 还处在发边线球
And Deacon's got it for a first down, but he stayed inbounds.
时间不挺的流逝
Tick, tick, tick. The clock keeps running.
还有时间！还有时间！
Clock's running. Clock's still running! Clock's still running!
留心！
On the ball!
真见鬼！快做点什么！
Goddamn it! Do something!
Hut!
这次克鲁想要掷球了
Crewe. He's looking to throw. Under pressure again.
快！加油！
Go! Get rid of it! Go! Go!
他把球传给麦吉特 他还有机会
He pitches it to Megget. He's got some room.
麦吉加油！
Here we go. Here we go. Go, Megg! Go, Megget!
加油！麦吉特
- Go, Megget! - Get him!
没人可以拦住他
He could go all the way!
但是……
But he won't!
真见鬼
Goddamn it!
麦吉特在4码处受到严重撞击 他受伤了
And Megget is hit hard at the 4, and he's hurt.
我的膝盖,天啊
My knee, man!
我们需要你的膝盖 都指望你了
You busted your knee for us, we'll bust our ass for you.
教练,我们要个替补
Hey, coach, I need a back!
一定要赢！
Just win this shit.
我去
I'm going in.
真的吗？教练
Coach, you serious?
当然
Yeah, I'm serious.
看看谁上场了
And look who's coming into the game.
你能做到
You can do it!
老家伙！你能笑到最后
Get that old ass of yours in the end zone!
我们会赢得比赛
We gotta win this thing! Come on!
等等,老头
No, no, no. Hey, old man.
绝对不行 你会把自己的命赔到这
Absolutely not. You're gonna get killed out here.
他们都跃跃欲试了 别担心,我会打好比赛
They've been trying that for years. Don't worry, I got the perfect play.
- 我不会把球给你的 - 看情况吧
- I ain't handing you the ball. - You don't have to.
内特·斯卡波罗 1955年海斯曼奖杯获得者
Nate Scarborough, the former Heisman Trophy winner from 1955,
上场打后卫
is gonna play tailback,
不过他上场主要也只能提供 精神上的支持
but he's gotta be in there more for moral support than anything.
邪恶战车！邪恶战车
Mean Machine. Mean Machine.
Mean Machine, Mean Machine Mean Machine
邪恶战车！邪恶战车
Mean Machine!
比赛还有6秒钟结束 比分落后7分
Six seconds left on the clock. Cons down by seven.
这一举必须得分
They must score on this play.
被让他们得逞！
Don't let them through!
进攻！就位
Down, set!
黑色99码！
- Black 99! - Come on, D!
Black 99! 一！二！
一！
Hut! Hut!
球给了大块头特里
The give is to the big man, Turley.
他被兰伯特拦截了
He's stopped by Lambert at the line for no gain.
太不可思议
No! Wait!
斯卡波罗捡到了球
The ball's picked up by Scarborough.
来吧
Come on!
得分
Touchdown!
真是精彩的一幕
What an amazing comeback, folks!
这将载入内布拉斯加州的 比赛史册
Taking a play from the old Nebraska playbook.
这一行动
The Fumblerooskie.
放松
Easy. Easy.
你还好吗？老头
You still alive, old man?
这辈子感觉从没这么好过
Never felt better in my life.
你这个变态,起来吧
You're a sick bastard. Come here.
All right.
现在囚犯队可以凭借额外的加分 不用进入加时赛
And now the cons are a mere extra point away from overtime.
邪恶战车
Mean Machine!
投票决定：我们继续打赢比赛 还是打个平手就够了？
Team vote: We go for the win? We go for the tie?
我们是罪犯 我们当然义无反顾
Hell, guys, we're convicts. We always go for it all.
不幸的是,这也是 为什么我们呆在监狱的原因
Unfortunately, that's why we're all in the joint.
凯尔泰克会怎么样？
What would Caretaker do?
把那黑板给我
Give me that blackboard.
来吧！
Yeah, come on!
Come on.
你是认真的？
Are you serious?
我不知道,这样打有点怪
I don't know. That play is wack.
绝对管用
It's gonna work.
会管用,来吧,上场
It's gonna work. Let's go. On the ball.
Come on! Let's go!
来吧大家上场
Let's go, y'all! Let's go!
我觉得没问题
I think it's gonna work.
Get them out there.
几分钟的休息之后 克鲁回到赛场
And wait a minute. Crewe is coming back into the game.
囚犯队会赢得比赛
The cons are gonna go for the win.
他们义无反顾
They're going for it.
克鲁在组织进攻
Crewe, trying to settle his team into formation.
但是看上去有点小问题
But there seems to be a lot of confusion.
来吧,快开始
Come on! Run the play!
特里,站在那边
Turley! Turley. Over here.
你站在这里,就这
Move your giant ass right here! Right here.
来吧！宝贝！
Come on, baby. Come on.
比赛正在计时 克鲁最好叫下暂停
The play clock is still running. Crewe better call a time-out.
来吧,克鲁
Come on, Crewe!
他们不知道我们在干什么
They don't know what we're doing!
就照我们计划的去做
Run the play we set up.
我觉得你刚才摔糊涂还没清醒！
I think you're still dizzy from that hit!
球快速传给迪肯
The snap is to Deacon.
是个骗局
It's a trick.
他扔给克鲁
He throws it to Crewe.
难以置信,他们做到了
They did it! Unbelievable!
囚犯队赢了
The cons win!
我们赢了
We win!
晚上洗澡的时候好好抱抱
Group hug in the shower tonight!
不用不用
Or not. Or not.
知道吗？
Well, there you have it.
一群残酷无情的罪犯 打败了
A bunch of ruthless criminals have beaten
维护公正系统的国家机器
the men that uphold our justice system.
罪犯也是人,克里斯
Criminals are people too, Chris.
现在！把钱包交出来
Now, give me your wallet.
什么？
What?
开个玩笑
Just kidding.
你有更多机会得分的,克鲁 你打的真糟糕
You got a lot of balls, Crewe. You played a hell of a game.
而且别担心 我知道你和凯尔泰克谋杀无关
And don't worry, I know you had nothing to do with Caretaker's murder.
我会支持你的
And I'll back that up.
谢谢你
Thank you, baby.
邪恶战车
Mean Machine! Mean Machine!
你太让我丢脸了 你居然赢不了比赛
You humiliated me. I can't believe you couldn't even win a fixed game.
他觉得自己要到哪去？
Now, where the hell does he think he's going?
他要逃跑
He's escaping.
警官,射杀那个人
Officer, shoot that man!
先生,那有人群
But, sir, there's people.
射杀他
Shoot him.
克鲁
Crewe!
上尉 我命令你必须射那个罪犯
Captain, I order you to shoot that prisoner.
射杀他！开火
Shoot him! Fire!
克鲁！
Crewe!
我命令你,上尉
Damn it, I'm giving you an order, captain!
克鲁！
Crewe!
块扣扳机
Pull the trigger!
就是个球而已！
It's the game ball.
嗨！
Hey.
把这个做你的战利品收藏把
Why don't you stick this in your trophy case.
- 玩不错吧?老头 - 当然
- You have a nice time, old man? - Yeah.
下一步我们做什么？
Yeah? Okay. So, what do we do now?
首先,我们要告诉大家 怎么狂扁昂格尔
Well, the first thing is, we tell the team where they're hiding Unger.
我等不及看斯韦托斯基怎么揍他了
Oh, I can't wait to see what Switowski does to him.
真是不错的比赛,先生
Great game, sir.
去小黑屋呆一个礼拜吧
That's a week in the hotbox!
谁TMD在乎啊?
Who gives a shit?
-=TLF SUB TEAM=- http://tlfsub.eastgame.net